CHP Codeex is a game-changing AI tool if
you use it the correct way. And in this
video, I'll show you how to use its
gamechanging features with realworld use
cases. So that by the end of the video,
you unlock new capabilities and get
ahead of 99% of people with this new
super app by GBT, even if you've never
coded before. If you don't know me, my
name is Jack. I built some last tech
startup with a gazillion customers. Now
I'm building my own AI startup and I
show you the exact stuff that actually
works. So, if you haven't already, grab
that coffee and let's dive straight in.
So, in this Codeex course overview, this
is what you're going to learn the
foundation and the five services, what
Codeex actually is, the five doors,
which platforms to be using, which
pricing. We're going to go through the
big three and why it's taking off right
now. I'm going to show you models and
speed routting. We're going to go
through co-work mode and cloud codecs.
We're going to touch on skill systems,
the three layer memory stack, plug-in
connectors, MCPs, automations. Um, we're
going to cover image gener design,
hybrid pricing, and then some of the
cool assets that we're going to touch on
inside this beautiful video. So, let's
talk about codeex positioning because
isn't chat GBT like that exgirlfriend
and we deleted a number like how she
come back, what is going on here? Well,
I'll explain why and why it's important
to think about this and how it fits with
the claude ecosystem even if you've just
been using chat GBT. So, um, the TLDDR
would be that it's basically not just a
code edit editor. It's kind of your
codework. So if you think that cloud
code for example has code and chat and
then also code work, it's bringing it
all together into one app. Some context
for this is that cloud code has gotten
worse which is why a lot of people are
moving over to use codeex and I'll show
you my strategy on what I'm going to be
using for both of them but it's
important context to understand. First
big thing to understand is it's powered
by GBT 5.5 and if you've got chat GB+
you can basically run with this
immediately. Um here's some kind of
benchmarks for you to see this. most
people having Codeex review their code
anyway as we currently stand. So, six
quick benefits, then we'll download this
together and go through everything. You
can pick it up on any device. It has
five different interfaces, whether
that's going to be in the Codeex app or
anywhere else. Agents will work while
you sleep. You have these cloud
sandboxes. It can run without you. Um,
you hit the limits way slower because
Codex is way more efficient at the
limits that you actually get. So, your
token stretch further. It reads your
whole codebase and it catches a lot of
what Claude is missing. Hence why most
people are using it for a review. Why is
this really freaking cool? You can pick
up exactly where you left off. One
codeex everywhere. Terminal ID, app
cloud, chat GBT, same login, same
memory, zero reset. So to download this
bad boy, all you're going to do is head
over to this website here, which is
developers.openai.com/codex.
And if you've never coded before, I
don't want you to be intimidated. I
promise you it's just like ChatGpt, but
with extra superpowers. So this is the
codeex app. It's got a very beautiful
interface. This is everything you need
to know. So first of all, you can start
chats like this and be like, "Hey there,
what is the date?" Okay, pretty much
just like chat GPT or Claude or anything
like that, we can begin conversations.
Now, a couple of things that you need to
know at the bottom here. Let me see if I
can zoom in a little bit just to show
you this. You have your permissions. So
default permissions is it will just ask
you your permission. Auto review,
basically, it's going to review
everything for you. And full access just
gives it access to just run and in claw.
This is what you'd be called like full
crazy unlock mode. So it can do anything
that you want to. Here we have both the
intelligence level which I typically set
to extra high. And then you've got the
model. So you can do 5.5, 5.4. Uh and
there's obviously other models there.
Obviously 5.5 is the strongest and what
you want you want to use. What's really
cool as well is they let you toggle
speed against performance. So you can go
even faster. Uh that increases your
usage a little bit. Down here obviously
this plus button. You can upload things.
You can change plugins uh documents,
spreadsheet, presentations. It's super
cool. So, for example, if I clicked on
spreadsheets, for example, I could ask
it to create one. And just to show you
how this user interface works, hey
there, do me a favor. Create for me an
example spreadsheet for a business with
revenue per month for the last 12
months. I'd love to see that. Thank you.
So, as you can see, what it's using now
is a spreadsheet skill, which we'll come
on to shortly. And then we're able to
see everything here within the actual
window. Now, when you're using codeex,
you'll notice on the right hand side,
you have the progress bar, which is
quite cool. It just runs through and
shows you everything that it's doing,
which is cool. Then also in this user
interface you can assume the left hand
side you can search you can access
plugins. Plugins is what codeex
basically calls skills. So if you skills
and claude that's basically plugins
within um codeex you got automations. So
we can actually set up automations and
I'll show you that in this video as
well. And then we've got this really
cool project tab which I think is one of
the coolest things and kind of makes
this a really accessible version between
co-work and code. So now we've done that
we can click on business revenue and
show you exactly what that looks like.
It opens up in the pane on the right
hand side and there you go. You can see
not only has it gone and actually
created some cool information, we've
also got a beautiful trend and we can do
anything that we liked with that cuz
this is a file but it's completely
edited. Then one of the things just to
do on a housekeeping perspective with
codeex is come down to settings. You can
check your rate limits as well here if
you want to. Gives you all of the full
detail. So settings, click on settings.
Now what I want you to do first of all
is if you're just someone who wants to
use this casually you can actually go
for everyday work you can toggle that on
and off if you want to. This here's an
interesting one. So when you open up
files, you can select where you would
like that to go. You can configure the
appearancer. So we can go light mode,
dark mode. We can go dark mode. Now I
know a lot of people in the comments,
they love their dark mode. We have
configuration. So you can basically
configure everything that you want to
within the actual system. Then on
personalization, you want to give it
some custom instructions. The one that I
like to give really is I just tell it,
hey, direct casual tone, no fluff, no
corporate speak. Um, don't use these
filler words. And I often like to say,
for example, I want you to look around
corners and think about problems I might
have and solve things. Um, basically try
to understand my intentionality when
you're building it. So go ahead and do
that. Then on memory, what I like to do
is enable memories. We'll touch on that
later. And skip to assisted chats. You
don't need to worry about that just yet.
And then the coolest little hack
actually, and I'm going to come back
over here now and change the appearance
back to live, is this pets. We can
basically have little pet, which I think
is cool. So you can select the pet that
you want to. Obviously, there's no
question that the fireball is the
coolest pet. So there's no doubt we're
going to be using this guy over here.
Now the next thing that you can do is
basically use folders. So this is really
cool. And now what I'd recommend you do
is go to chat GBt Claude and basically
give it this prompt which is the
following. Based on everything you know
about me, if you had to organize my
world into six buckets, what would they
be? And effectively what we want to do
in CEX is create six different projects.
One could be for your business, one
could be for your community, one could
be for YouTube, for LinkedIn, for your
clients, whatever it is. And all you do
is come to project, click on either an
existing folder if you've got one or
start from scratch. So I might come down
this folder here and I want to rename
this one. And let's just call this one
as if for instance something like glido.
Okay, which is what I'm using to
communicate. This could be all the stuff
that I'm doing in glido. And then I can
just create any chat I want to. I could
say, hey, go and do some research on the
best speechto text strategies in the
world. Whatever the thing is, we can
send that one off, which is fantastic.
And I can have all these different
parallel agents. Hey, who's the tallest
man to ever live? Okay, I can have all
these things working independently
coding for me and then I can just check
in uh on the ones that I want to and if
there's one particular that's
interesting I can come down here pin
that and that will now be in the pin
section but obviously if I don't need to
I can just unpin it then it sits in
that. So your world in codeex basically
should be having like these different
various different kind of like folders.
So one would be for glido. I might come
down and another one here which would be
something like um let's go and call this
one like community. And then literally
we just have all the ones they just run
down the left hand side and then
whatever you're working on you can
literally just come down select the um
requisite folder and they'll be ready to
go. Now one of the coolest things about
codeex is actually the way that it uses
skills that you can essentially just
tell it to create skills and they'll be
fully embedded. But also there's a very
cool hack that I haven't seen mentioned
anywhere else on the internet. So the
important thing to bear in mind is Codex
does make skills really easy. Think of
skills in the following way. You ask
Codex to do something. Let's just say
that you have an intro skill for YouTube
or a LinkedIn post creator or you had
like a business process. The standard
way we do this is we work until it gets
to a certain level and then you can ask
Codex to turn that thing into a skill
which means at any point in the future
you say, "Hey Codex, do this thing." It
will then go ahead and execute for you,
okay? Using what's called the skill
creator scope. So it makes it super
duper easy to go ahead and do. Now, for
example, if I come back over here, I
could say something like, "Hey, there I
would like you to go ahead and encrypt
for me a skill in which I give you a URL
and then you turn that URL into a bit.ly
link. I will give you my bit.ly API key
to do this. Then I want you to turn this
into a skill." And then, for example, I
just come over to bitly.com and grab
that API key. So, on Billy.com, I come
down here on the bottom left is API key.
It'll be just behind me. I come back
over now to Codex, give it the API key,
and then it can go ahead and create it.
Beautiful. Now, that's completed. What
we can do is just test this out in a
brand new chat. Let's open this one up
and say, "Hey there, do me a favor. I'd
like you to shorten and create a bit.ly
link for this glido.com." So, we can
just test this one out. Send that one
over and then it will basically turn
this into a bitly link for us. As you
can see, it's running the Python script.
It's done it. And just like that, will
that work? We open it up and beautifully
now. This introduces very nicely into
the user interface on the right side.
So, check this one out. You can see
we've got everything over here. I can
move this around. I can, if I want to,
check out new tabs, open files, do lots
of cool stuff. They've done some really
cool things with um Habers all connects.
Now, here's what I want you to do as
well because one of the biggest issues
is Jack. All my stuff is in Claude. What
the hell do I do? Well, I'm going to
show you what you do. You're going to
open up Claude or wherever you were
building skills previously. And on any
chat, you're going to give the following
prompt, which is this. Hey there, I'd
like you to get every single one of my
Claude skills, and I want you to save
them into a folder called Clawed skills
on my desktop. In addition to each of
those skills, I want you to add an
overview and an implementation overview
document that basically explains to a
different platform that if you were to
implement these skills, any background
context or any important information
such that I replicate these skills into
a different environment like Codex, send
that one off. And once you've done that,
what you're then able to do is come back
over to Codeex and literally tell it,
"Hey there, I've got all of my Claude
code skills on my desktop at this
location. I want you to go and implement
them and turn all of them into codec
skills for me." What that basically
means is you now have every single skill
completely duplicated in the Codex
environment. A complete seamless
transition. It's going to save you hours
of time. Now the other thing to look at
are these things called plugins over
here. So if you click on plugins in the
top left now you can see all the cool
ones here. So computer use is a
brilliant one. If you wanted to do that
you click on plus. You can say that
sounds great. We're going to install
computer use and you may need to give it
some permissions. Browse use is great.
That just lets it go ahead and do things
in the browser. And computers, as you
might have guessed, it just means it can
do stuff like control apps and do
various different things. So, for
example, if I come over to new chat, I
can say, "Hey there, open up my
glider.com app and go to my settings,
please." And send that one off and
you'll be able to see it should do that.
And as you can see, guys, it's actually
done that. It's open this by itself. And
if I come back here and say, "Awesome.
Do me a favor." Now, what I'd like to do
is click on preferences in the app for
me. Now, what's really cool is it won't
actually take control of your PC. So,
you see how I'm here. I could be using
this. I could be touching various
different things, doing various
different things, and it will do
everything in the app by a series of
commands without taking control of your
desktop. So, look at this. If I click on
it now, I should be on preferences, and
it's done that instantaneously for us,
which I think is so freaking cool. Then,
when you want to add in your skills, all
you're going to do, guys, is come down
here and just search one that you want.
So, for example, if I like notion, I
just click on notion, for example. I'm
going to reference memories and chats.
That's cool. Which is allows chat GPT to
reference relevant chats memories when
sharing data with notion for helpful
responses. That's cool. Click on install
notion. You'll then be prompted to sign
in once it opens up in a brand new
window which is great. We come down,
click on continue and then it sends us
back over to Codeex and then that link
will be completed and now it can do
various different things for us inside
notion. As you can see, notion has a
beautiful tick. Once again, the one I
recommend that you do connect to as well
is GitHub. So, we're going to come down
here. We're absolutely okay to reference
chat. Come down and install GitHub. Now,
if you don't see the thing you want to
connect to here, say for example, you
want to connect to something like
Firecrawl. It's not there. What you can
do instead guys is come down here to
create and click on create a plugin and
you can literally say hey there I would
like to connect to firecrawl for example
or whatever it is and then literally it
will go through the entire process of
doing that. So it came out here I can
just get rid of this um and I just say
let me know any information you need for
me to create this custom plugin and then
literally it'll go through the whole
process and then you can connect it
directly even if it's not in the openai
library. Now, these features are
incredible. Where Codex really shines is
its ability to create code, which I'm
going to show you how you do, and not
only that, but how you can pull in any
project or any design that you've seen
anywhere and actually use that inside
codeex. So, as we know, we can build
anything that we want to. But the
reality is that the best design model
out there is Claude, which I'm going to
show you how you integrate Claude in
here. So, you actually never need clip
codecs. But when I'm building UIs, the
place I always go to is Lovable. The
reason for this by the way is even this
dashboard here which I show which I
built for my community this was all
built with lovable. So when I'm building
apps and applications effectively what I
tend to do is build it in lovable first
try a few different places I get the
best design and then I bring that one
over. So let's say for example we want
to go and build a dashboard and then we
want to use this inside codeex. How
would we do that? Well we come over here
and we throw this one in. So I've got
this prompt here which is to build a
modern SAS analytics dashboard called
pulse. just something random so we can
build something. Um, Lovable is really
niching down and making the apps
beautiful that you're building there.
So, if you're somebody that wants a
little bit of an easier journey, it's
really great for that because you can
post it, publish it, do loads of cool
stuff. It's been my experience. It just
tends to produce really good freaking UI
on one shot. You can get there different
models, but it's just really cool. Then
it gives you all the different updates
about everything it's doing. You can add
references from different projects.
Really freaking cool. And then when
that's complete, we have this wonderful
thing here that looks great. And I can
come down and have a look at it. And
again, really freaking sle. I've got all
these different aspects and capabilities
here. One of the things you can do
within Level if you want to. So, for
example, these sidebars don't do
anything. Let's come back over and just
give it a prompt. Hey there, dude. I'm
clicking on the sidebars. They don't
link to anything. Could you just add
different pages for each of those
sidebars, please? Okay, we're going to
send that one off. Now, Lable's going to
go ahead and do some navigation looking
for us. Now, interestingly here, if you
did build it here, you can have all the
databases in a certain particular
location, which is fine. and you don't
need to connect anything else. What
we're going to do is actually take this
and we're going to bring it into Codeex
and import it as one of our projects so
we can do additional work on it using
the superpower within Codeex, which is
fantastic and I'll show you exactly how
you do that. But the important thing is
that when you know how to do this with a
dashboard, you can essentially do it
anywhere you want to. This is the
easiest way to get it up and running in
the system. So, we'll get this one done.
It's going to add in the sidebar pages.
Then, we'll be able to bring it over to
Codeex. Beautiful. So, that's complete.
Let's give it a test. If I click on
users, do they appear? They do indeed.
This is really freaking cool. I like
this activity. Got everything we need.
So, what we're going to do now is come
over and click on publish. So, this now
basically turns it into a website. So,
we can test that if we want to, which is
great. Continue. That's fantastic. But
what we want to do as well if we can, is
come over to GitHub like so and sync
your project to GitHub and just connect
GitHub to lovable. So, I'm going to come
down here, click on connect. Okay,
great. So, now we have something in our
GitHub repo which we can copy because
Codex is great. ChatVD 5.5 is fantastic.
It's not the best at design yet. So,
we're going to lean on different models
and softwares to get the better design.
Now, I've come back over to Codeex. What
I want is a project for general things,
right? Or I can just create a random
chat. If it's just something I'm never
going to return to, I'd go for a random
chat. Just click on a new chat. Then it'
be like, "Hey, dude. I want you to shoot
over to this GitHub, clone it, bring it
in, and then we're going to do some
magic on it." And then going to come
down, throw the GitHub repo in, and then
we should be ready to rock and roll.
Now, bear in mind that we actually
connected our GitHub earlier, so it
should be able to go there directly and
grab it for us. Beautiful. And now
that's completed. You can see it pulled
it down to pulse- chronicle. You can
click on that. This is now all of the
code that we created. But we want we
want to look at the visuals guys. We
don't want to read about the app. We
want to see the app. So when you click
on it now, you'll see the entire thing
within Lovable, which is freaking really
cool. Now, one of the cool things I can
also do within Lovable if I want to is
bring up the terminal. I can add many
various different pages. But one of the
coolest features about this is something
that you might not expect, and that is
the fact that you can use the brand new
chat GPT 2.0
image generation model which is the best
one on the planet now specifically at
getting great text and we can do this
natively with inside the app without any
need for any other integrations and the
way that codeex does this is it
basically creates an image without
forcing you to leave the platform and it
uses this image gen scum for example let
me show you what I mean so I'm going to
say something like hey there dude what I
would like you to do for me is add in an
image on the left hand side dashboard uh
there's a jibli sty style um golden
piggy bank that fits in nicely. And why
don't you make that something like I
don't know 4x8 or whatever dimensions
make sense in the bottom left that would
fit nicely in the dashboard. So I'm
going to send that one off. Hit that
off. And now you're going to see it will
now actually physically go ahead and use
the chat GBT generation and build it
into the app. And that was one of the
reasons I wanted to bring an app in here
because you can now see and look how
this kind of scales by the way how
responsive that is based on the
dimensions. Really really freaking cool.
Then look, it's using an image gen skill
which is native within the codec. And
then it will literally add it into the
dashboard for us. And just like that, we
now have the Jibli golden pig in there.
All done, all added in perfectly. But
there's one hack that I haven't seen
anybody else mentioned, and it's the
only way that I create software with AI.
Now, and I'm talking about the three
brain strategy. And the idea of this is
that each model has its strengths and
its weaknesses. And we can effortlessly
tag in the expert model, whichever is
best, based on the specifics of the
thing we're doing. So if it's something
image based or something design based,
we may want to bring in Claude. If it's
like analyzing two hours of video, we
can bring in Gemini. And we can do all
of this inside codeex. And so for
example, the best way to bring in Claude
is to toggle the terminal. And would you
look at this guys? Now we have the
terminal at the bottom, which is cool.
So let's just get rid of the sidebar so
we get a little bit more space. In fact,
let me bring it back out. Now all I'm
going to do is come down here and type
in Claude. And when you say Claude's
name, Claude appears. Now, if you
haven't installed CL, I'll put a link on
screen for a full master class about all
this sort of stuff. So, you can get in a
lot of detail, but you just basically
run it and he's there. And now the cool
thing is that Claude can now work on the
projects. What else can we do is we can
run up as many of these Claude instances
as we actually want to. So, now we have
a second Claude running. Really freaking
cool. So, I might say something to
Claude like, "Hey, dude, could you do me
a favor? Could you just change the
animation or the effect? When I hover
over MR and active users, the animation
looks a little bit basic. Could you just
improve that for me?" Beautiful. Now,
let's test this guy out. If I hover over
it, let's see what we're dealing with.
Look at this, guys. Much cleaner
animation. And that's how we leverage
it. But it isn't just that. What we can
also do is bring in Gemini, which you
can do by using this plugin here. I've
got a full video breaking down the free
brace system, so I'll link it on screen
for you so you can check that out. But
basically, all you do is come down here,
copy this, come back over, and just say
to check GBT or Claude. In fact, let's
get rid of Claude code real quick. You
just say, "Hey, I'd like to go ahead and
install the Gemini CLI and basically
connect this GitHub repo, please." and
then come down and basically just give
it the URL. And this fixes very nicely
onto one of the coolest features in
Codeex, which is its ability to automate
things repeatably. Now, you can use
automations within Codeex on the top
left by clicking on automations right
here, which is really cool. And this has
features that do not exist in Claude
right now. Hence why I'm saying that
this does feel like a co-work/ chat
all-in-one kind of super app. So,
essentially, this is a good way to think
about these automations. It's like cloud
code but on a timer. What do I mean by
that? You write a prompt, you pick a
schedule and it runs in the background
without you. Effectively, really super
duper simple. Um, you can do it
standalone or in a conversation if you
want to. So standalone is a fresh run
every time. No memory of the previous
one. So this is good for like daily
reports and audits. For example, I could
come over and say, look, summarize
yesterday's get activity for standup. I
can click that if I want to. Or really
simply if I want to what I can do new
automation I could say something like
daily brief and then down here I could
say hey do a daily brief for me go ahead
and check my Gmail my calendar all those
different things and find for me the
latest news in a automations and give me
five crisp clear insights that
straightforward but even if I wanted to
simplify this and just come down like
this I could pick when it happens the
project that it's in the work tree
basically all this information and also
how I want the reasoning to be obviously
we want it to be extra high, which is
fantastic. Now, if you want it to happen
randomly in the chat, that's fine. But
if you say it's something to do with,
let's say, your business, I can click
that, click on create, and then you can
see all of your automations here. And if
I want that right now, I just go boom,
run right now. Then if I go over to
Glido, I will actually able to see this
thing running for me instantaneously.
And you can see it working by clicking
on automations up the left hand side,
and it pops up that cool. The other cool
thing you can do is you can actually ask
it to automate within the thread, which
is really freaking cool. So, for
example, and you can even set reminders
in the chat. So, I could say, for
example, hey dude, in 2 hours time,
could you just remind me to refactor
this database? And look at this guys.
Yes, I'll set that up as a wake up in
the chat. It's done. I've created a
reminder. So, every 120 minutes, it's
going to come back and give me that. So,
we have the reminders on the chat level.
And then we also have it at the auto
automation level, which is awesome. So,
we go refactor. Look at this. It's even
pops up here. Refactor database
reminder. And this is the exact chat
that's happening. And this is the daily
brief again that you can pop up and have
a look at. So if I come back over to
automations, I click on this, you can
see all the details. Or if I come down
and click on play, it starts the
automation and mimics exactly what it
would do. And as you can see, that's all
completed. And it's even deleted the
automation. So that's gone. So this is a
complete cheat code in the actual
system. Very very very very cool. So the
key here is it can be standalone or in a
thread. It can be on a work tree or in
your live code. And there are three
levels of trust obviously that we can
authenticate. We can do lockdown touch.
We can edit inside the inbox or we can
do it with no guardrails on the full
access if we want to. So this is really
good for daily commits and bug fixes, PL
babysitter. You can do skill autotuning,
deploy watches and even repo cleanups.
And that takes us on to the big question
which is what should you be using right
now? Should it be anti-gravity vs code,
the clawed app or this brand new codeex?
Now before we can understand that you
have to understand one final thing about
the codeex app and that is to deal with
its brain. Now in Codex there's three
levels to the memory. Okay, we have
agents.m MD. This is the thing that we
created at the beginning of the video.
And by the way, if you ever want to
within Codex, you can say, "Hey, open up
my global agent.MD file. I would like
you to make some amendments." And as you
can see, you can do this within
conversation window or if you prefer,
come down to settings here. And if you
come down to personalization left, this
is your global MD file. In addition to
that, Codex will actually remember
things from your conversations, right?
This goes it's autogenerated. It learns
from past things, preferences, that sort
of thing. And then finally, the most
interesting feature on here is something
called Chronicle. Now, Chronicle
essentially takes screenshots of your
screen. So, it can get what we call
screen intelligence of the stuff that
you're doing and that you're working on
so it can then inform and answer better
questions. So, it has way more context
about what you're doing. What's
important to bear in mind here as well
is it got a 6h hour autodee. So, it
won't store, you know, what you were
ordering controversially at 11:00 p.m.
on Valentine's Day. It will delete that
as it goes. The way that you access this
Chronicle, obviously, it's something you
need to toggle on. But, if I come down
to settings, and the way you get it is
in settings under personalization, and
as you can see, I have Chronicle
Research Preview. This was only
available on the Pro Max plan, the $100
a month plan, and it's not available in
the UK and Switzerland due to our very,
very tight data. Actually, I don't live
in the UK anymore. I'm in I'm in
beautiful Dubai, but you get the idea.
So, I can come down here. I can enable
this and it basically explains cost uh
privacy uh prompt injection. Okay, so
you basically go through if you're
comfortable with it you can continue.
Now the benefit of this once you've set
it up is the fact it has more context to
help you do various different tasks. And
then once you've given it the
accessibility you can try it out and now
it's good to rock and roll. Basically
describe what I'm working on right now
and suggest how I can use codeex to
help. I hit enter and now we're
literally using chronicle which is a
really cool way of describing it. As you
can see, I'm checking whether the screen
history is live first. Then I'll look at
the latest capture frame and recent OCR
to figure out what's going on. Chronicle
is running, the latest capture is fresh,
and then I click on this and would you
believe it guys? It's literally just
captured my screen like this, which is
cool. And it can do that. So say for
example, you're doing a I'm talking to
people in my community or I'm helping
out with how to build website. Like I
did a big session yesterday, hours just
giving feedback on their websites, help
them improve. But I'd be like, "Oh,
dude, I saw a website that was about, I
don't know, beautiful Laqua. what was
that or like how could I have given
better feedback. We now have the screen
intelligence that can cut across
everything that you're doing on the app.
And as you can see, it's come back and
give us interesting information. One a
quick little hack as well by the way is
you can say something like, "Hey there
dude, go ahead and build me a simple
dashboard um covering why cyan is the
best color, right? You give it a
question, add that in there." Now, one
feature you can do is something called
steer, which is you've given it a
prompt, but it's not quite finished yet.
And what you can do with this is
actually guide codeex in its build
without actually interrupting it. And
you do that by say something like
actually also include a section for why
green is the second best color. Okay,
you write that down. You send that in
there. And I have this steer which is
submit without interrupting the model
after next model call which is cool. So
this one here I'm now steering the
conversation any particular direction.
Now for this I actually compared the
pricing and the usage you get from both
chat GPT and Claude. Now bear in mind
it's like comparing two sons very I mean
we can't choose between our children or
maybe we can I don't know but the point
is that like the on paper the pricing
actually is very similar. It's 20 100
200 for pro pro basically max 5 max 20.
Now typically speaking the the usage you
get on OpenAI is more generous than what
we're seeing like for like on Claude. I
should also call out by the way right
now there is a promo one that like
amplifies your usage. But the key detail
that a lot of people miss is the fact
that Codeex uses around four times fewer
output tokens per task. So even if you
said that Opus was more powerful or like
theoretically even if it were to be
cheaper on paper, it's four times as
much work to get to the same outcome. So
it's just something to bear in mind in
terms of your actual token usage. Now
what am I personally using? I am on the
Pro 5X for chat GBT. Obviously, from my
point of view, it doesn't affect my life
if you buy it or not. I just want you to
actually win. I'm going to come on now
to what my recommendation is and what I
would do if I were in your shoes with
all these options on the table. So, if
you're somebody who is tinkering on the
weekends, you're learning the tools,
just go for your $20 track subscription.
That will be fine. You will get most of
your stuff done there. And you can tag
in other models like a Deep Seek. I'll
put a link on screen so you can check
that out. That will go a lot further
than you think. And that is really
generous and do quite well. if you're
shipping side projects and SAS daily and
you know the pro 5x plan when you hit
limits from plus. So don't go straight
to this one. Start with your $20 one and
only if you hit the limit then consider
upgrading. And if you're running an
agency you're doing eight hours a day on
Codex, you may want to move it up and
bump it up as you actually hit those
usage limits. And so with all of that
information in mind, what does it mean
for Claude? Well, what we're not saying
is we're never using Claude. I really
like Claude. And Claude is the best
design agent on the planet. If you're
not using claude at least on the $20
subscription, you are leaving a load of
design firepower on the table. So
whether you want to integrate it into
codeex, which you can do now, or another
means, it is an absolute mustave. My
philosophy is that the best way forward
is what I call the multi-brain strategy
leveraging the best models for the
particular use case in hand. And now you
understand exactly how to get ahead of
99% of people using codec. The next
thing we need to do is to learn how to
amplify those skills by building super
skills inspired by a genius called Andre
Apathy. And we're going to learn that by
watching this video right