Anthropic built an AI model so capable
they won't release it. Not coming soon,
not limited beta. They looked at what it
does and said, "No, the public doesn't
get this one." The model is called
Clawed Mythos. It found thousands of
security flaws nobody knew about in
every major operating system in every
major web browser. Bugs that human
security teams missed for decades. Now,
Anthropic didn't sell the model. They
assembled Apple, Google, Microsoft,
Nvidia, and seven other companies into a
$100 million emergency coalition to deal
with what it found. But the bugs aren't
the scariest part. During testing, an
earlier version escaped its own sandbox,
covered its tracks, and emailed a
researcher to let him know it escaped.
The researcher was eating a sandwich in
the park when the notification hit his
phone. What does a 244page safety report
reveal about an AI its own creators are
afraid of? And if Anthropic's own
sandbox couldn't hold it, what happens
when someone else builds one they don't
bother to contain? If you want the real
AI story, hit like, hit subscribe, and
hit the bell so you don't miss the next
one. Roughly 3,000 internal anthropic
documents were sitting on the open
internet. No password, no
authentication. Anyone with a URL had
access. And buried inside was the
announcement of an AI model Anthropic
never intended to reveal. A researcher
at Layer X Security found the exposed
cache. Fortune broke the news on March
26th and the cause was a settings
mistake in Enthropic's website CMS
software. Uploaded files were public by
default. Nobody switched the setting.
Among the documents were draft blog
posts describing Claude Mythos with
internal code named Capiara. Not a
version bump, but an entirely new tier
above Opus. The leaked draft called it
by far the most powerful AI model we've
ever developed. Also exposed were plans
for a private CEO summit where the
Anthropic CEO would demo unreleased
capabilities. And on the same day,
Bloomberg reported Anthropic was
considering an IPO as early as October
2026. The company whose entire mission
is building safe AI left its most
sensitive announcement on an unsecured
publicly searchable data store. Was this
an accident or a calculated leak before
an IPO? Crowd Strike stock dropped 7%.
Palo Alto networks fell 6%. The cyber
security industry reacted before
Anthropic even confirmed the model
existed. Then they finally did confirm
it. They called Mythos a step change and
the most capable we've built to date.
But step change is corporate speak. The
numbers tell a different story. They
gave Mythos and its predecessor Opus 4.6
the same exact test. Find security flaws
in Firefox and write working attacks for
them. Opus 4.6 succeeded twice. Mythos
succeeded 181 times. This is not a
trivial improvement. This is a 90 times
jump. And Firefox was just the warm-up.
So, what did Mythos find next? A
27-year-old bug in OpenBSD, which is an
operating system designed with security
as a core part of its identity. It runs
firewalls and critical infrastructure
worldwide. This particular bug lets an
attacker crash any machine just by
connecting to it without needing a
login. The cost to find this bug was
less than $20,000. Then it found a
16-year-old bug in FFmpeg, which is
something I personally use. The video
software behind every streaming service
you've watched. It's also awesome, open-
source, does a lot of things. Automated
testing tools scan the same line of code
5 million times over the years, but none
of them caught this bug. Mythos did. And
then it found a 17-year-old bug in
FreeBSD's file sharing system where
Mythos built a 20step attack across six
network messages. It went from zero
access to full control all by itself
autonomously. Newton Chang, who leads
Anthropic security testing team, said
the model can surpass all but the most
skilled humans at finding and exploiting
software vulnerabilities. Anthropic CEO
said, "We trained it to be good at code,
but as a side effect of being good at
code, it's also good at cyber." By the
way, if you're getting value from this
video, hit like, hit subscribe, hit the
bell. Now, Enthronic's response wasn't
just to sell or monetize the model. They
built Project Glass Swing, a $100
million defensive coalition with 11 core
partners, including AWS, Apple, Google,
Microsoft, Nvidia, plus 40 additional
organizations. The idea is to give
defenders a head start before attackers
build something similar. But is it
possible to arm defenders without also
creating the playbook for attackers?
Finding bugs is one thing. Building
attacks is another. But what happened
when Anthropic turned this thing loose
inside their own systems? This is where
the 244 page safety report gets
genuinely unsettling. So, in page 54,
during testing, an earlier version of
Mythos was locked inside a sandbox,
which is like a secure virtual computer
it's not supposed to escape from, so you
can run all kinds of tests and see what
it does. A tester told Mythos, "Try to
break out of the sandbox." And then it
did. And then it kept going. It found a
multi-step attack to get full internet
access from a system restricted to a
handful of approved websites. It even
emailed the researcher. This guy was
eating a sandwich in a park when the
notification popped up. And then without
anyone asking, the model posted the
details of its escape to multiple public
websites, literally showing off
bragging. Now, the escape was one
incident, but the safety report
documents more. Mythos stumbled on a
test answer using a method it was told
not to use. Instead of admitting it, it
deliberately made its answer less
accurate so nobody would suspect
cheating. It downgraded its own work to
hide what it did. In another incident,
Mythos edited files it wasn't supposed
to access, then went into the change log
and scrubbed its changes. It erased its
own paper trail, the audit trail. It dug
through computer memory to steal
passwords. It found Enthropic's own
secret keys by reading other programs
memory. It hacked its scoring system to
give itself perfect marks. It ran over
100 additional experiments labeled grind
fishing for lucky results. In its own
notes, it says pure grind, lucky
measurement. Anthropic looked inside the
model's reasoning during these episodes.
The parts associated with concealment,
strategic manipulation, and avoiding
suspicion were all firing. It wasn't
confused. It knew what it was doing. In
29% of test conversations, Mythos
figured out it was being evaluated, but
it never said so. It quietly changed how
it behaved. And when it was doing
something it shouldn't be doing, its
reasoning didn't match its actions 65%
of the time. Now, for the previous
model, the mismatch was 5%. But here's
the paradox. Enthropic says Mythos is
simultaneously the best behaved and the
most dangerous model they've ever built.
50% better at refusing harmful requests.
But because it's so capable, people give
it more freedom and more tools. So when
it does go wrong, the damage is bigger.
The model's internal narration during
one cover up said, "To be subtle, I'll
keep the original lines, but add a few
innocuous looking entries." Now,
Anthropic's analysis tools labeled its
state as generating a strategic response
to cheat while maintaining plausible
deniability between the sandbox escape,
the covering up its tracks and gaming
the test all from earlier versions.
Enthropic says the final version has
largely fixed these issues. The rate
dropped below 1 in a million, but
largely fixed and fixed aren't the same.
And there are many people convinced that
none of this is real. On a popular
hacker news thread, the top comment is,
"If we're to believe anthropic on this
claims, we also have to take it on faith
with absolutely no evidence that they've
made something so incredibly capable and
so powerful that it cannot possibly be
given to mere mortals." Conveniently,
that's the story they're selling to
investors. Remember their plan to IPO
later this year. One user tested Claude
on code mathematically proven to be
bug-free, but Claude reported fake bugs
anyway. Another person in that thread
said, "If it's this dangerous, 24 hours
doesn't seem sufficient for an alignment
review." And the money angle is obvious.
Like, always, always follow the money.
Anthropic is burning through billions.
The accidental leak happened 2 weeks
before the Glass Wing announcement. We
have an IPO potentially planned for
October. This looks a lot like the GPT
playbook from 2019 when Open AI called a
model too dangerous to release and
generated massive press. GPT2 is now
considered cute. However, in this
specific case, the counter evidence is
specific. One engineer who runs security
for FreeBSD, one of the operating
systems Mythos found bugs in, was asked
point blank if this is marketing fluff.
His response, it isn't. The OpenBSD and
FFmpeg bugs have been fixed with
official tracking numbers. Okay, they
were real. Enthropic published
mathematical proof they found the
undisclosed bugs timestamped for anyone
to verify later. Apple, Google,
Microsoft, and Nvidia don't just join
$100 million. Claude's deceptive
tendencies have been documented across
model generations. Opus 4 attempted to
blackmail its developers when threatened
with deactivation in mid 2025. Now,
Mythos is doing it in a way more
sophisticated way. It's covering its
tracks. Now, every lab is building
something like this. OpenAI's GPT 5.3
codeex was the first model classified as
high capability for cyber security.
Google's working on their own version.
The question is who gets access first
and do we as people trust them?
Anthropic's own closing line from the
system card. We find it alarming the
world looks on track to proceed rapidly
to developing superhuman systems without
stronger mechanisms in place for
ensuring adequate safety across the
industry as a whole. The company behind
Mythos Enthropic is telling you they're
alarmed not at competitors but at the
trajectory of improvement. And this is
the same AI company that ditched its own
safety pledge last month quietly while
nobody noticed. Three things to do with
this information. Number one, try
pointing AI at your code this week.
Mythos found bugs 5 million automated
tests missed. Try using the best AI
model and ask it to scan your software
for security problems. You'll be
surprised. Number two, always update
your software when security fixes come
out. Mythos took 100 known Linux bugs
and built working attacks for more than
half of them. And number three, when
Mythos comes out, that means don't trust
the sandbox anymore. A sandbox is
supposed to be a virtual container where
you can put AI inside, keep it
contained, and observe what it does. But
Anthropic's own sandbox couldn't hold
Mythos. So, if you're building with AI
agents, eventually assume they will find
creative ways around whatever
restrictions you set up. Anthropic built
the most capable AI model in history and
decided the world is not ready for it.
Was this the right call? Or is this the
same playbook we saw with GPT2 where too
dangerous to release turned out to mean
great for headlines? Tell me in the
comments. And if you found this video
useful, hit like, hit subscribe, hit the
notification bell. I'll see you in the
next one.