Club Code is the world's number one
design agent, but 99% of people get AI
slop because they make one mistake. And
in this video, I'll show you my new
system that lets you build beautiful
slides and designs worth thousands in
minutes using 20 universal design
principles in any style that you want to
so easily, [music]
even if you've only ever used PowerPoint
before. And this is brand new. And if
you don't know who I am, my name is
Jack. I built and saw my last tech
startup with a gazillion customers. Now
I'm building my own AI business and I
just share here the stuff that works. So
if you haven't already, grab that coffee
and let's dive straight in. Now I've got
a lot of really cool stuff to share with
you in this video and I want to show how
you can pretty much build any slides
that are gorgeous by just using your
words. These are in. PowerPoint is out a
lot of the time. I mean look at this for
example. These were created uh right
here with one shot. I wanted to play pay
close attention to things like the
numbering, the lettering, the logos. All
this stuff was given by just giving it a
website. It grabs all the brand assets,
all the colors, even the logos, and was
able to deliver this crisp design like
this. And here's another example for
Grind Coffee. Exactly the same. And it
the level and positioning consistency
are incredible. This is all under
underpinned basically by these universal
principles, which come into a second.
Because the big problem is we order
Picasso and Mr. bean shows up and this
is very capable. It's like a 500 IQ
interm, but we've not been treating it
properly. So, let me show you how you
make slides that look like AI didn't
actually uh make them. So, let's take a
look at this. And by the way, this works
on any URL. The system and skill that I
built that does this on autopilot. It's
a GitHub link. I'll put it down below so
you can just literally grab that and
implement this entire for a consistent.
It's very, very cool. First thing to
understand though is that design is
code. Every great brand is a tiny set of
variables, color, type, scale, spacing.
Once you rob a token, the design writes
itself. And my theory was if we could
define what excellent design looks like
and codify that and build a system
around it. And Claude is capable enough
that it could actually execute on that.
The only challenge was identifying what
is excellent design and how do we
reverse engineer that? And I've gotten
results that I've never gotten before.
And I've had like 11 comments in the
past seven days like, "Jack, how are you
doing your slides?" Hiding your slides.
Hence why I wanted to make this video.
So essentially, we come from code like
this into basically presentations that
look really cool. So let's look at the
old versus the new and I'll show you
exactly how you do this. So it's the
same content, two different universes.
PowerPoint default, you know, defaults
to this really old school style of doing
things. Same with Canva, but you're
still dragging things over and there's
thought involved. And the idea here is
that instead of using something like
PowerPoint or maybe even Canva, you can
actually just get this to be
programmatically created. You are only
limited by your imagination with this
incredible technology. So the other
issue that you get with most slide decks
that you see and websites for that
matter is that every website kind of
looks the same. It's got that really
weird orangey claw type feel to it. It's
like five prompts, five different purple
gradients. That's always really common.
and the defaults are doing all the work
and it's becoming so obvious what an AI
website is now but it just drives people
away and you're kind of getting them. So
that's the big issue here, right? And
the big problems that we've got is
sameiness. It's generic AI slot. Um if
you give it a bad prompt, in other
words, garbage in, you get garbage out.
Um you get drift. So basically, it just
changes over time. And there are no
underpinning design principles that are
actually working. Hence why we have what
I call the AI sloth apocalypse. Like you
let a backend dev loose on your
front-end code. It's chaos. We cannot
allow it. It's out of control. So here's
the thing. It's not magic. It's actually
measurable. So 20 rules. Each one is
codified. Each one is checkable, bicep
ratios, etc. Just to really help AI
explain what that physically is. So, let
me show you for example what that
physically looks like. So, these are the
20 universal design rules for AI design
superpowers. So, research back. They're
pull from very very premier resources
and explain what they are and how this
whole system and skill actually works.
If you don't understand why design is
good, we're never going to be able to
actually go ahead and build a design.
So, let me bring this out a second. So,
what am I talking about? And by the way,
these very slides you're seeing right
here, including images, which I'm also
going to show you how you do
programmatically like this, all done
with code in one go. Like that's
basically where we're at now. I can
build this for anything I want to. And
you'll learn those two skills as well.
So the first one, and this is comes out
to a really cool book, which is called
don't make me think. So you shouldn't
really have to think. And the idea of
this is one idea, one slide. The second
one is it should be glanceable in 3
seconds. Basically slides are scanned.
They're not studied. 3 seconds is the
budget. If you can't get the point of
three, you don't have a slide. You have
a document. So number three is maximum 7
ideal 3 to 5. This is to do with the
number of things that are on the page at
any one time. You can go down in more
detail if you like to. I just want to
give you the bird's eye overview and how
this works. 40% empty. So white space
isn't where the design ends. It's where
the design lives. Cramp slides feel
anxious. Hero slides want at least 60%
standard at 40. And this idea that if
you go into any premium brand, right,
like you'll always find like an an
abundance of space. You also see this at
Apple. So, we want to reflect that in
our designs. Number five, 5% of
everything. This is a really cool one.
Actually, this one came from TV. The
idea is that no critical content within
5% of any edge. And by the way, if you
want to skip these design insiders to
get straight into the building, I'll
timestamp everything down below for you
so you can skip ahead. But I really
think this is worthwhile doing cuz this
is like the crux what makes it so cool.
So, as you can see, we don't want
anything touching the edges. And if you
come over and have a look at this for
example, can you see we have this
beautiful border all the way around the
side and it did the exact same thing
with the grind slides. And again, this
was all done with I just gave it URL and
this is what it put out. Like this is
all following the principles and if you
understand it, you'll get what what I'm
talking about. Cool. Number six is going
to pick a ratio drive everything. So
this here is the golden number. This is
what we see this golden ratio all
through nature and the world. It's very
very very cool. Um, basically you you
have every number related to that. So
you have say your first pixels 100, you
divide that by 1.618 and so on and so
forth. That's how you get something that
just looks magical and correct rather
than rand. Don't just eyeball it. Use
actual ratio. It's like a good little
design hack. Four sizes per slide. No
more display subhead caption. That's the
budget. If it's size signals you didn't
make a decision. And the cool thing is
guys, you don't even know need to know
all this stuff. This just for your
knowledge. like we give this to AI as
it's kind of coding infrastructure it's
rule book and it runs away with it. So
28 points or readable from row 10. So
body text this is basically just talking
about like how the sizing that it needs
tight to big loose to small again this
is line height some good good principles
on that 60 characters most this is
really good especially presentation the
slide shouldn't have paragraphs to begin
with if they do cap line length of 60
characters anything wider and the eye
loses its place between the lines so
when we're building design systems you
actually do have to be specific with the
size and actually the length if you want
to reproduce high quality consistently
that's what is required Done. So number
11 is going to be about ratios. You can
check it out in more detail. 60 30 to 10
is a classic one. So this is 60%
dominant, usually the background, 30%
secondary, and 10% accent. That's often
what we say for color theory in rooms.
It's very, very cool. Then we've got the
one accent. Uh that's a budget as you
can see. And each of these different
designs, guys, has only one accent,
which is cool. Color is never alone. 8%
of men are red, green, color brand.
Encode meaning with shape, weight,
position, label, icon. Color reinforces
never substitutes. So again, you can go
down these. You got eight pixels always
to do with the margins. One grid,
everything stops. 12 column grid. Again,
it's more to pixel nomics if you like.
Distance equals relationships. This
one's really cool. Proximity is the
cheapest grouping signal. Items related
to each other um of like this level
apart. So this is basically saying these
two things here are obviously like
separate, but if they were together, for
example, like this text here, they would
be viewed when you look at the screen as
one like unit basically. to that has to
do with like just kind of codifying
distance. So what I did, I tried to find
all the best design insight and there
might be more. So this list might grow
and if you've got any great suggestions,
limit it down below, but these are the
best ones I found. And essentially,
we're just codifying those design
principles. 80% of the ink should be
data, which is cool. Strip every chart
pixel that isn't carrying meaning. No
3D, no gradients, no drop shadows and
bars, no redundant legends, uh top left
or invisible. This is really cool. Eye
tracking is unambiguous. Attention
enters top left and swoops right. So
again, we even got this nailed down and
pick a mood and stay in it, which is
really cool. So this is basically our
entire system, which is really freaking
cool. So the question is, well, how do
we then take all this beautiful design
stuff and actually build something, get
into the build. So what you're going to
do is you're going to come over here,
you're going to click on this GitHub
right here, and then we're going to head
over to this guy. And all you're going
to do, and as you can see, we've got the
power design there. We've got all the
different images. Um, you can see
everything there rocking and rolling. So
you're going to come over here to code,
and you're going to click on this. And
then you can head over to your
integrated development environment of
choice. If that sounds like I'm speaking
Spanish, I did just launch a full Claude
code course in my community. I cover
everything from foundation setup,
building a website with insights and
design hacks I've never shared anywhere
before. It's really crazy power
features, memory system, the whole
thing. I'll put a link if you want to
check this out down below, but if you
want to level up massively, I can I can
share that with you. So, what we've done
is we've copied this. Now, I'm going to
go ahead and build this in anti-gravity.
And then we can kick some butts. And now
we're in anti-gravity. I'm just going to
come down here to open folder. I'm going
to give a brand new one. I'm going to
call this one something like power
design, which is the name of the repo.
And this one specifically is for slides.
But I'm going to expand this I think
over time to pretty much encompass any
kind of design framework. I'm really
excited with the results I've got. And
we can see together just how this works
for anything. So I'm going to say, "Hey
dude, do me a favor. Go ahead, download
this repo, clone it, and then
familiarize yourself with it." And then
we're just going to throw in the URL
like so. Bada bing, bada boom. And then
we are rocking and freaking rolling. Now
this repo is a fork of a ripper called
Vault Design which has brand systems for
everything. And I thought that would be
a really great basis for this because if
you come over to brands here, you can
see it's got essentially the brand style
for loads of different brands that you
can play around with as inspiration.
What I often recommend you do is look at
the HTML behind it. So this is good for
inspert if you want a quick idea. But
what we're going to do here is basically
for this process. So basically you're
going to paste in a URL. So this could
be your website. Once we've done that,
firecrawl is going to go and extract the
DNA basically from that or you can just
use one of these pre-built things in the
library. Then you're going to give it
what you want it to look like and then
it's going to generate slide and then
you can iterate on it following between
design rules. Sound really cool? Let's
freaking do it. So I think we should go
ahead and do uh clickup.com, right? So
let's just do clickup.com and then we're
going to come down and say these are the
firecrol credentials. Now, the reason
that we're using Firecrawl, and I really
like Fire Fuel is because a, it saves on
tokens, grabbing things. But most
importantly, it can actually extract the
brand identity from the website super
duper easily. So, this is ClickUp. This
is the example that we're going to do
first of all. But if I come over here to
this, come into fc.dev. Literally, just
grab your API key from the homepage.
Just API. Come back over and then we
just throw in our credentials into
anti-gravity. Or if you've got the net
connection, you can just put it there.
And just like that, guys, it's
downloaded all the stuff. So, we've got
a brand style MD full 10 section brand
spec which is great for in the repo's
template. Then we've got the actual
clickable logo which is awesome visual
theme color palette. This actually went
over and took screenshots of the website
to get a little bit of sense of it
visual brand. All the components look
like I said SVG. So now it is ready to
rock and roll. So I'm going to say
awesome. Do me a favor. Go ahead and
just create for me three slides in a
slide deck as a sample using this style.
And while Claude is cooking in the
background, let me show you how this
process connects together cuz
effectively it's 3 minutes from any URL.
That's all I gave it to a deck with this
skill. How does it work? First thing
we've done is we grabbed the repo tick.
We picked a website or gone from the
brand library. We chose clickup frol has
extracted the brand DNA. Fantastic.
Claude has generated the deck or way to
do that. And when that's done, we can
actually either share this via GitHub
and versel CLI if we want to, which
means we can actually share this HTML
deck with anybody. For example, these 20
rules thing that I designed, that's what
I did at the final stage. I built all
this stuff out. And there we go, guys.
Look at this. This, by the way, is one
shot. I have not added anything else to
this. It's all done this itself. Look at
this logo. It's even got the logo in the
bottom left. And the sizing, the
spacing. This is really, really cool.
The cost of tool sprawl. There we go.
And it's even got that cuz look at this
guys. If I find the website here, you
can see how ClickUp has this like
gradient type of thing where it goes
from that's a pretty cool feature from
one type to another. It's added that in.
It gets that which is really freaking
cool. These are just really freaking
crisp. I'm really I I think for a first
shot this is cool. And obviously you can
just go ahead and do what it wants to
add that runs on your work guys. Like
for honestly like this is ridiculous.
I'm really super duper impressed with
this. And again just coming out to show
what it looks like. Get started. It's
free. Watch a demo and see if this
button works. If I do that, it does
actually open a new page and open into
that which is cool. Now, obviously, I
know there'll be 17ear design experts
that comment saying, "Well, actually,
this should be here." I get that you
could improve this. Of course, you can,
but for a first shot, like it is just
really freaking cool. So, let's give it
another example from a completely
different brand and see how it gets on
with it. I'm beautiful. As you can see,
I literally on the left hand side, I
said, "Hey, now do Strive. It's done it.
Financial infrastructure." And by the
way, guys, it did it in like I don't
know, it tells you how long it took,
right? How long did it take? Uh, like a
couple seconds. It didn't take very long
at all. It was very, very freaking
quick. And if you're wondering why I've
come over to the claw desktop app
instead, it's because this one has 4.7
native in and I wasn't using the
terminal. So, if I bring this one over,
let's have a look at what we've got.
Payments for the internet. It's got a
nice beautiful subtle hue to it. Like I
think a lot of people design expect
loads of whisbangs and like less is way
more sometimes. You can see these really
use the premium space. Building payments
takes months. Stripe takes an afternoon.
Really crisp. One API every part of
running money online. really freaking
cool. And then it's even got a different
contrast which is decent like that.
That's nice. And then start integrating
your minutes. Cool. I mean like it's not
like it's a very professional cool thing
that you would feel comfortable sharing
in a corporate environment. I think
that's really freaking crap and these
are awesome. And bear in mind even the
ones that I showed you earlier guys all
designed with this system. So why don't
we now instead take it one step further
because design is one thing typography
colors HTML animations. But what we
could do to take this another level
further is actually bring in the world's
best image generation models. And when
we do that, we can get something that
really creates an incredible wow factor.
So, for example, these are our ClickUp
slides, right? Which I think are pretty
decent. And I I think they're very, very
cool. But what if I wanted to get some
images to throw in there like on one of
the slides? Well, what I personally use
is I use this website called Kia.ai.
It's basically Willy Wonker's Emporium
for APIs for like image video
generation, that kind of thing. and you
basically create an account. You can
throw like5 $5 to $10 in it. It's really
freaking cool and you get really good
prices in my stuff. I'm not affiliate
with these guys. It's just the one
honestly that I've been tending to use.
So, we're going to go ahead and grab
your API key on API keys on the left
hand side. It's just Kia API hyphen key.
Go ahead and grab one of your API keys.
Then you come back over to Claude and
basically what you're going to do is
say, "Hey, here is my API key for KIA
AI. I would like you to use the brand
new chat GPT image generation model to
generate me. Let's do three more
slides." And on each of those three
sides, I would like one image uh one
graphic integrated in the below style.
And then add your API key in here. And
then for your actual style, one of the
things I like to do is if you come over
to something like midjourney.com as an
explore, you can actually search for
different graphical styles. Or maybe you
go to Google and you say um illustration
simple, something like that, right? Try
and find different ideas and graphics
that you think are really cool that
would really sit uh and kind of
complement that. Let's have a quick
look. So you can get a good idea. I
recommend using these image gen
platforms if you want to. Maybe you like
this one. I would never take one from
Google when I'm building anything. But
just as a for instance, let's say that
you really like um let's say this fox
design. Actually, this is kind of
quirky. This is like millennialesque
type of thing, right? So, let's say we
want to grab that and do that more. And
in fact, even on Pinterest. There we go.
This is a really cool one. This is like
a really consistent style. So, let's
come over here and let's say we want to
download the image, which is cool.
Download that to our computer. Then you
can swing back over and then we
literally just pop it in here by
uploading. It is the last file that I
downloaded on my computer. Cool. And
then just throw in the API key.
Beautiful. So now we have this. It is
eight slides. Let's check out what it's
done. Okay, let's have a quick scroll
down. And wow, this is literally exactly
the style. It's given it a little bit of
a sticky table. I didn't ask it to do
that. That's insane. And again, can you
see from the first cell to the first
balloon? This looks ridiculous. Like I'm
super impressed with how it's just done
that. like that looks like the view was
sat in a big stuffy corporate office
building with a big mahogany desk and
this came across on the slide. You may
perk up a little bit. You may be able to
pay attention the rest of the meeting.
This is really freaking impressive.
Obviously, this rabbit hole goes way
deeper. That's what I cover in the big
course if you'd like to learn more. But
for building slides, this can do it
programmatically for any brand. You
enter the website in and you get to
enjoy beautiful things just like this.
Then if you say, "Hey, I want to go
ahead and host this and share it to
other people." We can post that on
Versel super easily. And all you need to
host Versell is a GitHub account. And
then secondly, you need a Versell
account. And you basically just say to
Claude, "Hey, I want you to connect to
GitHub and Versel via the CLI." And once
it's connected to those two things, both
your GitHub and Versel, it is able to
post basically your entire website super
easily. Now, building beautiful
presentations is one thing, but
presentations are just one part of a
multiaceted design ecosystem. So, what
we need to do next is learn how to
leverage other tools to get you further
ahead, which we're going to do by
watching this video right