Today we're going to walk through how to
make a TikTok automated slideshow using
a reference image. For example, what
you're looking at here is a TikTok
slideshow. It even has automated
trending music applied to the slideshow
even though you can't hear it right now,
and it's using a reference image of a
particular dog so that you get
consistent scenes throughout. And we're
going to walk through automating this in
both N8N and make.com. I have Kevin with
me today. He's an AI automation expert.
Kevin, you mind giving your quick intro?
>> Sure, Ding. So, hi everyone. My name is
Kevin. I'm 32 from Malta. I've been
doing AI automations for the last few
years. What I love about this is the
reference image part in the sense that
what you're seeing here,
if you have any UGC, any specific images
about your brand that you want to have
consistent through the slideshow that
you're creating here, this is the video,
the
automation that will do it for you.
We'll show you both make.com and N8N so
you have
the ability to do it on your own with
just changing one node, one module. So,
you can get be up and running with this
very quickly.
And we're going to walk through a very
specific example here of pet slideshows.
For example, promoting a pet-related
product. However, you can actually tweak
this automation very easily for your own
use case. Okay, so we're going to dive
into a specific example so you can see
what it really looks like, but it's
very, very easy to tweak this to your
particular business, your particular
product. For example, if you want a
consistent product photo across the
entire slideshow, that's easy to do as
well. We'll start with make.com. That's
a little bit easier. If you're here for
the N8N tutorial, you can just fast
forward to the second half of this
video.
>> [snorts]
>> So, here in make.com, very
straightforward sort of automation or
module in terms of what you need to
edit, there's this edit here module. And
the idea is that you give it
the
image for your UGC,
sort of image that you want to use right
here. So, you just drop that in there.
You give it a topic, and here I wanted
something very, very, I would say,
generic. The more information you can
give it here, the better the prompts
that will come out of this in the next
stage. So, we'll speak about that in a
second. And then you have the number of
slides there as well. So, you can define
how many slides you want to have in your
show. The way we've set it up is that
the first image, which is the
this one right here, will get appended
to the start of your show as well. So,
if you have your first image that you
want to start with, this will
automatically take that into
consideration. In other words, if here
we have three as the number of slides,
the final slideshow you would end up
with four images. Your first UGC image,
and then the additional three.
And, by the way, you can change the
link, obviously, to your own image. So,
if you have a Google Drive with the
images, just make sure the image is
publicly viewable by anyone with a link.
Or if you have a Google Drive folder,
you can replace that variable value. We
have those three variables right there.
And this is where we get into the
image prompt right here. So, we've
already set this up for you, but if I
just go through this so we can sort of
see what that is composed of. The idea
is that we're saying to Open AI, you
generate prompts for short-form TikTok
live slideshow
where each slide is generated by an
image edit model. So, we're giving it
this is sort of what you do. This is
what you will receive. So, it will
receive the topic, it will receive the
number of slides, and we're giving it
specific information about how we want
the format to be returned. Nothing that
you need to change from your end. It's
just already given to Open AI and the
module right here.
Then we're asking it to give us a
caption.
And we have some information around what
the caption or how the caption should
look. We're asking it to give us a
title. In terms of the title, we have
information there as well. And then
we're giving it some additional
information. A slide one is the hook.
Then we have specific output formats.
You could go through this, you could
make it your own.
Or you can just run with this and then
tweak to get to the result that you want
as well. So,
that is what we have right here in this
system prompt right here. And then we're
passing along the topic, as you can see
from the pulsating first module, and the
number of slides. So, all that
information is being
passed along to this Open AI module.
This will then call Replicate. So, this
is the image generator that we are using
in this in this case. And specifically
here, we're using Nano Banana for one
specific reason, because it takes this
input image, this reference image that
you would have given it for your UGC,
right? For the initial first image that
you want to have in your slideshow.
And
if we go back here, we're calling
Replicate. And in this case, since I
said I want three
as the number of slides,
the way this has been set up right here
is that this Replicate is getting called
three times to generate those three
images that we'll use in our slideshow.
And then once we get that back, we're
using the Blow Data to create a post to
post directly to TikTok. We're changing
the inputs here. We're generating the
image prompts. We're actually creating
the images. And then we're using those
images to post on TikTok via Blow Data.
And let's walk through real quick how to
set up accounts, especially Replicate,
if people are not familiar with that. I
highly recommend Replicate because you
just pay per usage as you're generating
images and videos. So, you don't have to
do a monthly subscription or anything,
and you have access to all the latest
image and video models. And just
depending on which ones you use and how
much you're using them, you just get
billed for that usage. So, it's a really
nice option. So, if you're not
generating any images or videos this
month, you pay $0. There's no
subscription fee unless you're not using
it. All you need to do is come in here,
hit try for free. You can sign in with
your GitHub, which is a free account.
So, if you haven't created it, you can
create that first using your normal
Google account. And then once you're
signed in, I would just go in here and
look for
the image model that you want. For
example, Nano Banana. I just chose that.
And then you get to this place where you
can even test out your prompt right here
and reference images directly on the
Replicate playground, on the Replicate
website. So, you can see what different
models and the different outputs that
these models would give. For example, if
I put in Nano Banana and I choose Pro, I
would be able to see and compare the two
image generators side by side. If we go
to the dashboard, we can see all the
image generations that we would have
done. We would see how much each image
generation costs, so you can also keep
track of how much you're spending, and
you can see how much you're going to pay
Replicate in this case at the end of the
month. If we go to make.com and I go to
call Replicate right here,
over here I have my token. So, the idea
is that you will need to insert your own
token right here. And to get that, what
you would need to do is go to your name
right here, click on API tokens, and
then you create a token right there. So,
you give it a name,
hit create token.
And then this will create that token for
you. So, you just copy that. And then in
make.com,
you just paste this in here.
So, what is important is that you leave
bearer as is. There is a space right
here. And then you paste in the API
token that Replicate has given you. And
this is the same for N8N as well. Once
you've set it up, it's a one-time thing.
So, then you can run with that, use the
same token
the next time around as well. And then
Open AI should be pretty
straightforward, guys. You just sign up
for your account at platform.openai.com,
I believe, and then grab the API key and
just put it right there. And like Kevin
showed, there's a nice little link you
can click right right where you set it
up. Yep. So, I just clicked Open AI
account API keys. That opened that for
me, and then I create new secret key,
give it a name right there, create
secret key.
Copy that, and just drop the API key in
there, and then I would have that new
connection. I can also give it a better
name right here. So, if I have multiple
ones, I would know which is which as
well. So, for Blow Data, very simple and
straightforward here, I
added the create a post, which you will
have already here if you are importing
the workflow. So, if you import the
blueprint right here, you will have
these nodes right here. So, what you
would need to do is click on the Blow
Data
module right here, hit add, and you will
need to insert the Blow Data API key.
Simple, straightforward to get this. So,
you'd go to settings, you'd go to API,
you'd go to copy right there, and then
in make.com, you just paste that in
there. Hit save, and then you would be
able to choose from any of the platforms
that you would have already connected in
Blow Data. And that, if you go to
settings, you're able to log in with any
of the platforms that you would then be
able to connect to in make.com. And, by
the way, if you guys get stuck with any
of this and need help in the Blow Data
app, on the bottom right corner, there's
a support chat. And the AI agent's
pretty good at helping you debug
workflows, but if it can't help you, I
typically check support tickets within
48 hours or so. Awesome. Should we do
N8N?
Yeah, that's it.
All right. So, the idea here is pretty
similar to make.com. And we have an
editor sticky note. So, I would come in
here. I would give it the
UGC image that I want to use. Same thing
as before, I would give it the topic.
And I can also choose the number of
slides. So, in this case, I just had
four.
With the way N8N is configured,
we're
querying Open AI with the same system
prompt as we had before.
And we have the same inputs right here
as the user inputs. So, in this case, we
have the dog food UGC and the number of
slides.
This,
in turn, generates the image prompts
that we then pass to Replicate. So,
there's the same idea here.
We call Replicate, and in the sticky
note here, I said insert API key here.
So, what we did before with replicate
going to API tokens, we need to grab the
API token from replicate and inserting
it right here in
n8n. So, if we go to authorization, we
just need to replace that
over there with the replicate API token,
right? In order for you to be able to
run it under your account.
And uh most common error I see here
sometimes people will like remove the
space between bearer and your API token.
So, just make sure you don't change
that, guys. It should be bearer space
and then paste your API token. If we
look at the output here, we'll then
generate the four images. So, here we
have replicate image one, image two.
So, image one, image two, image three,
and then image four right here.
What we're doing then is combining
everything together to pass it to
TikTok or to post it on TikTok via Blo
Dato. So, here is the same idea.
Blo Dato account. If it's your first
time connecting it, you hit create new
credential. You put in your Blo Dato API
key, which again you get you get from
settings API. So, you just copy that
right there.
You go into n8n and you paste in your
API key in there.
And once you're in there or once that is
done, you can then choose your platform,
which is TikTok. And we've already set
up everything right here. So, you choose
your account. You This is already being
mapped to the texts, the media URLs, the
slideshow titles. What we're also doing
is just enabling this auto add music,
right? So, that is if the sound was to
be on, you'd be able to hear the
background music that Blo Dato
automatically picks for you. So, this is
enabled here and is the same story right
here. If I look
at make.com, we have add music to
slideshow. So, that is the auto music
feature that Blo Dato takes care of for
you.
And there are a couple of other options
for TikTok as well that people like to
play with. Uh so, for example, you can
post these as a draft on TikTok. So,
there are many people who will like
automate the creation and then choose
the particular song that they want
within TikTok. If you're trying to um
jump on a particular trend or particular
trendy sound, okay? That's an easy way
to do that. And you want to schedule the
slideshow for a particular time, you can
either specify an exact time or just use
next free slots. Uh
a lot of people, including myself, I end
up just using next free slots. What it
means is like you can say, "I'm always
going to post on TikTok at like 10:00
a.m. and 2:00 p.m. every single day."
And then you just have to create content
and fill up your open slots like this.
So, over here under the calendar
feature, I can go to weekly schedule at
slot. I can choose my accounts right
here. So, I can choose my TikTok
account. Then I can say, I don't know,
Monday to Friday at 10:00 a.m. That
would be one of the slots, right? So, it
was just the next available slot.
make.com
would speak with Blo Dato and put the
publishing of this specific slideshow in
that time period.
Yep, cool.