If I had to start learning Claude from
scratch today, this is exactly how I'd
do it. Because here's the thing, you're
paying at least 20 bucks per month for
Claude, and you're probably only using
about 2% of what you're actually paying
for. I spent the last 2 years using
Claude every single day for my job, for
my business, for this YouTube channel.
And if I had to start over tomorrow, I
would not do it the way I did. I'd skip
over about 80% of what I tried, and I'd
learn these 13 things in this exact
order. So, in this video, I'll walk you
through my step-by-step syllabus for
learning Claude from scratch, starting
with the one you've already used. Number
one is Claude chat. You can go to
claude.ai, ask a question, and get an
answer back. You can access it from your
browser, your phone, or your laptop. And
it's all the same Claude, all the same
conversation. The thing that really
separates Claude chat from something
like ChatVT is what it can create.
Claude creates diagrams, tools, and
visualizations right in the
conversation. You can click through,
drag sliders, actually work through the
problem instead of reading about it.
Claude also builds artifacts which go
way beyond widgets. You can have Claude
build a PowerPoint deck, a Word doc, an
Excel sheet, a full website, even a
working app. All of that inside of chat.
Now, these are static, so they don't
update on their own, but there is a
version that pulls live data, and we'll
get to that. But first, you need to give
Claude access to your tools. Number two,
connectors. This is where Claude starts
plugging into your real work. Connectors
wire your tools directly into Claude.
things like Gmail, Drive, Notion,
Calendar, and Slack. Claude can read
from all of these apps directly and even
perform actions in them for you and on
your behalf. You might have Claude read
and summarize a Slack channel or send
out a message to your team for you. If
you're working on a project, you might
get Claude to read all of your
documentation in Notion or Confluence so
it has the full picture. Connectors work
across your whole Claude account once
they're connected. And later, I'll show
you how you can start automating tasks
inside of these apps using routines.
There are hundreds of connectors to
choose from with more being added every
week. They work using MCP or model
context protocol which lets Claude make
a request to the connected software to
do something. You can configure your own
connectors as well if the app you want
to connect has an MCP. Connectors is
when Claude starts doing real work, but
to keep that work organized, you need
the next one. Number three, projects.
Project lets you organize your work into
self-contained environments, each with
their own chat history, instructions,
and knowledge. You can manage the
knowledge of a project by uploading
specific documents or giving it access
to particular connectors. Every time you
chat with Claude in that project, the
knowledge is automatically there. You
can give it specific instructions or
even share the project with your
colleagues so they're working from the
same setup. Here's my setup for
generating proposal documents. Claude
has all of the context from the
templates, asks me the right questions,
and handles everything from there. Each
project I have has its own separate
memory, too. So, context inside a
project stays inside that project.
Projects really start to come alive when
Claude can actually act on your real
files. And for that, you need to step
off the web. Number four is Claude
Desktop. So far, we've been using Claude
on the web, but Claudei is barely
scratching the surface of what's
possible. There's actually an app you
can install on your Mac or PC for
Claude, and it's not just to wrap around
the chat models. It gives you the
ability to use some of the more advanced
Claude products and features like
co-work, code, and routines. If you've
only used Claude in your browser,
install the desktop app. The next four
things on this list all live there.
Number five, Co-work. And now we're
finally getting somewhere. Co-work can
see every file in a folder you pointed
at. It can open them, edit them, create
new ones, organize them, and even run
scripts. When you use co-work, you give
it a task and it goes and does that
task. It can create a PowerPoint for
you, save it to your documents, and then
go and edit that same document later.
It's when AI starts to do real work. And
co-work is built for people who don't
code, but still want the power of the
Claude code agent hardness underneath.
But the thing is, co-work doesn't get
blanket access to your machine. It runs
in a virtual environment, and you pick
the folders it can see and edit.
Projects are useful here, too, because
each project gives you a natural file
system barrier. This is the rung where
most people's jaws drop because for the
first time, Claude is doing real work on
real files instead of just talking about
it. Co-work also unlocks a different
kind of artifact, one I promised
earlier. Number six, live artifact. Live
artifacts are the same idea as artifacts
in chat, but instead of being static,
every time you open one, it pulls fresh
data through your connectors. This means
that you don't have to go and regenerate
your artifacts, which burns a bunch of
tokens. Instead, you can build them once
and have Claude fetch new data from your
connectors to populate that artifact
every time you open it or refresh it,
but now they're permanently useful. And
these are built inside of Claude
Co-work. And Claude can even help you
build them for you. Just go into the
live artifacts menu, hit new artifact,
and Claude will build whatever you need
to create. You can connect your tools,
build a custom dashboard that's actually
useful, and even share that with your
team. This is one of the first projects
I get people to build when they're
learning co-work because it brings so
much of it together for them. It's a
real aha moment because they see Claude
building a real persistent business
asset. Number seven, skills. And this is
the one that most people will end up
using more than anything else on this
list. A skill is just a folder, and
inside that folder is a file called
skill.md with instructions for how
Claude should do a specific job. Claude
is pretty intelligent, but it doesn't
have the domain knowledge required to do
real world tasks, especially ones that
are specific to your workflow. That's
where skills come in because they
package up knowledge, scripts, and
contexts so that Claude can invoke them
when it needs to do a specific job.
Claude has a bunch of pre-built skills,
and you can even get them from the
customiz menu super easily. One of those
pre-built skills is skill creator, and
it's a skill that lets you create your
own skills. The part that makes skills
different from everything else in this
video is that they work everywhere. The
same skill runs in chat, co-work, and in
the PowerPoint extension. They can even
be shared with other people. I used
about six of them to create this video
you're watching right now. Brand voice,
scripting, hook generation, thumbnail
creation. Skills are the multiplier.
Every other product on this list gets
dramatically better the moment you teach
Claude how you actually want things to
get done. Good skills are hard to find,
and the bad ones will waste your tokens
or worse. So, I'm building a vetted
marketplace for the skills I actually
use. There's the links in the
description below if you want to be on
the wait list. Number eight is Dispatch.
Dispatch is the bridge between your
phone and your desktop. You can hand off
a task from the Claude app on your phone
and Claude does the work back at home on
your desktop with all the same files and
all the same connectors. You get the
result back on your phone. And Dispatch
is a fundamental redesign of the
traditional AI workflow. Because up
until now, we've been actively working
with Claude to get our work done. But
this flips it on its head because
Dispatch is designed to give Claude a
task remotely and then have the work
completed and given back to you when
it's done. It's one shared conversation
across the two devices. So you can pick
the task back up on your computer once
you get back from your walk or the cafe.
So co-work and dispatch handle your work
on your computer. But if a lot of your
day is actually spent inside other apps,
that's when these next two come in.
Number nine, Claude in Word, PowerPoint,
and Excel. These are enthropic
extensions that put Claude directly
inside of Microsoft Office. It's the
same Claude you've been using, but now
it can actually read your slide deck or
your spreadsheet while you're editing it
live from within the app. This is great
for working on a file live with AI
because you might have Claude generate
the first draft of a slide deck from
co-work and then go and open it up
yourself and continue working on it live
in PowerPoint with Claude right beside
you. There are extensions for Word,
PowerPoint, and Excel. In Word, it can
draft, rewrite, and reformat documents
in your tone. In PowerPoint, it reads
your slides, your fonts, and your color
schemes. So anything it creates stays on
brand. You can create full slide decks
in minutes. And in Excel, it can build
detailed financial models, analyze
multi-tab workbooks, explain every
formula with cell level citations, and
update your assumptions without breaking
any of the dependencies underneath.
These extensions share context with each
other when you have multiple files open.
So if you're working on an Excel model
and then need to update a PowerPoint,
you can do it without reexplaining
anything. Number 10, Claude in Chrome.
This is a browser extension that turns
any tab into a place where Claude can do
work. It can read what's on screen,
click buttons, fill forms, manage
multiple tabs, and run multi-step
workflows from start to finish. You can
trigger the Chrome extension from
co-work or from code, or you can even
talk to it directly from inside of
Chrome. Really, it it's whatever fits
the task at hand. The thing that really
sets this one apart is that you can
record a workflow once and then Claude
learns the steps. So, if there's a
clicky repetitive task you do every
Monday, you can teach it and schedule it
so it happens automatically. Once Claude
can move around your apps and your
browser, the next thing you'll want is
for it to actually create the visual
stuff for you. Design is Claude's visual
workspace. It can build slides,
infographics, posters, social posts, one
pages, and even full wireframes. It's
the same models, but the output renders
in a designable canvas instead of
dumping the message into a thread. I
asked Claude for a five slide pitch deck
for a fake AI consultancy. It structured
the slide deck, the layout, the copy,
all of it. And then I can just ask
Claude to change it. I can even export
these as PDFs, a PowerPoint, HTML, or
push it straight to Caner if I wanted
to. If you've ever opened a blank Canva
template and st it for 10 minutes,
that's the problem that Claude design
solves. You can use this to vibe Design
Apps, too. It can build wireframes,
highfidelity frontends, and once you're
happy with it, you can hand it off to
Claude Code to actually develop the back
end. Number 12 is Claude Code. Claude
Code runs in your terminal or inside of
the desktop app and it's the most
powerful way to use Claude and you don't
even need to be a developer to use it.
Most people think Claude Code is just
for coding and it is incredible at that.
But it will happily do almost anything
else you can do on your computer and
it's particularly good at go to market
workflows. Think outbound content SEO
and marketing. Here's the part that
matters the most with Claude Code. It
has a context window around five times
bigger than co-work so you can run long
complex jobs without losing the thread
and you can see every file it touches in
real time so you can guide it. You can
give it different levels of autonomy
through permissions. Ask me before every
step to go for an hour and tell me when
you're done. And because it works inside
a real project folder, it remembers your
standards, your file structure, your
conventions every time. Here's what I
actually use it for. Claude Code runs my
entire content operation. It finds
ideas, writes my scripts in my voice,
creates thumbnails, SEO optimized
descriptions, and builds lead magnets
that go with each video. It also runs my
client work after sales calls. It takes
my meeting transcript and writes a
proposal. It builds assets for clients.
It does pretty much everything for me.
That's what makes this different from
everything else on the list because it's
not a tool that I open. It's the
operator of my business. If you want a
full walkthrough of how I set up my
Claude, drop a comment below and I'll
make that video next. But the real
leverage with claude code is when you
start taking work off of your plate for
good. Number 13, routines. This is the
one that runs while you're not there. A
routine is a saved tasks that executes
on a schedule. When a webbook hits or
when something happens in one of your
connected apps, it runs on Anthropic's
cloud, not your machine, so your laptop
doesn't even need to be on. Here's one
of mine. Every morning at 9, Claude
scrapes the Anthropic blog, finds
anything posted in the last 24 hours,
and posts to a summary into my news
channel on Slack. But the real unlock
isn't scheduled routines, it's event-
driven one. I have a routine that fires
the moment Fireflies finishes
transcribing a sales call. Claude pulls
the transcript, extracts the action
items, and files them in my second brain
and slacks me a summary before I've even
closed my laptop. No clock, no waiting,
no more opening anything. The call ends,
the work happens. This is the rung where
Claude stops being something you use and
starts being something that compounds
because every routine you build is
permanent leverage. set up 10 of them
and you've handed yourself an entire
workday back every week forever. I walk
through exactly how I run mine, the five
levels, the schedules, the web hooks,
the gotchas, and if that's where you
want to take this, that's the next video
to watch. Thanks for watching.