So Higsfield has access to all of the
best AI image and video generation
models. And Claude lets us talk to
Higsfield and build custom skills and
agents and schedule all of these
automations to run while we sleep. And
when we combine these tools, we're able
to actually scale up our content because
we can ideulate and we can generate 100
times faster than the average human
could. So today's video, I'm going to
show you guys how we're able to turn
Claude into a creative agency. So real
quick, let me show you guys a few
examples that I was able to generate in
literally 5 minutes with one prompt.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I mean, those are incredible. I think
that this second one's probably my
favorite. Like the zoom in on the
product, the detail, all of the
animations in the background, the music.
I mean, this is incredible. Even this
detail here, think about how long this
would have taken you if you either
wanted to edit this by hand or, you
know, shoot this with a studio and with
a paid actress. It would have taken so
much more time and resources. And like I
said, I was able to generate all of
those outputs just by talking to Claude
with a prompt that looked something like
this. So, before I show you guys these
conversations and exactly how I did it,
let me show you how we connect Higsfield
to Claude. So, if you don't have a
Higsfield account, go to higfield.ai and
you can sign up. You will have to get on
some sort of subscription, but once
you're there, you basically want to come
to this page that says MCP and CLI. And
we're going to first of all connect this
to Claude in the web. This is just your
typical Claude chat that you've probably
been using for months now. You're going
to go to the settings and you're going
to click on connectors and you're going
to have to add a custom connector. So
down here you can see that I have
Higsfield as a custom connector. So go
ahead and click add custom connector.
And you're basically just going to call
this, you know, Higsfield or if you want
to call it something else. I don't
really know why you would. And then
you're going to copy this command right
here. And back in Claude, you're just
going to paste that in. Hit add. Mine
says it's not going to work because I've
already done that, but yours will
connect. And then basically it'll prompt
you to sign in. So you'll hit configure.
It'll take you to the Higsfield OOTH.
You'll sign in with the account that you
just created. And then you will now have
Higsfield ready to go. And then if you
want to click on configure, you can
basically change the permissions. So if
you only want it to be able to do
certain things in your Higsfield
account, you can limit it to do that. Or
you can come in here and you can just
say, hey, always allow all of these. I
don't really care. So however you want
to get that set up. And now whenever
you're in a cloud chat, if you go over
here and you look at your connectors,
you can see that Higsfield is right
there. And you can just prompt it to
create you images with that or videos
with that or whatever you want to do.
Now it will be able to actually talk to
Higsfield as you can see. So, just to
start off and show you guys a few quick
examples, what I said here is build me a
headphone brand from scratch. I want you
to do research, build the branding,
build the product catalog, and for each
of them, I want you to generate assets.
So, a product photo, an Instagram ad,
and a UGC video. And I told it to use
the Higsfield MCP for all of these
generations. So yes, what we could have
done is done all this research on our
own or taken all this research from
Claude, put it in a Google doc and then
went over to Higsfield on our own and
found all these different AI image and
video models and just generated all of
this stuff in the interface. We could
have done that, but in today's video,
I'm showing you guys how you can
essentially just treat Claude code or
Claude as the interface to do all this
stuff and in a more consistent and
repeatable and automated fashion that's
really going to help you scale much more
than if you were to do this all
manually. So, as you can see, it does
the research. It looked at the market
and now it's helped me build a brand
called Murmur. And we have stuff like
positioning, target buyer, voice, visual
identity and all this stuff. And it
created three different products. So an
overthe-ear which is the most expensive.
We've got wireless earbuds and we have
open back wired headphones once again.
And then it just goes ahead and
generates all the stuff. So all these
images and videos that you're about to
see were just minimal input. It was
literally just, hey, build me a brand
and build these things. And now we have
this first photo of our Halo product
which looks very nice. We've got this
Instagram ad which came out a little bit
duplicated with the text for some
reason. But if we wanted to fix that,
all we'd have to do is say, okay, edit.
And then we could give it a prompt
because it knows the exact reference
image and it knows this what we're
talking about. And I could just say,
hey, you know, we have two different
headers in here. Remove one of them. So
you could iterate really quick on that
there. And you could also click animate.
So it's basically the same type of
prompt. and we can say, "Hey, turn this
into a video where, you know, the
headphones are spinning in a circle and
floating in the air, whatever we want to
do." So, that's the ad. And then we have
this video, which is basically just a
person listening to music, wearing them,
and smiling at the camera. So, you can
see though that video looks really good.
Like, the person looks very real. So,
we've got our second one. We've got the
picture right here. We've got the ad
right here. That one looks much better,
actually. And then similarly, we have
this video with music of a person
putting one of them in their ear and
then smiling at the camera. And then we
have the exact same thing for our final
product. We have an image, we have an
ad, and then we have a video of someone
using the product,
as you can see. Then I said, take the
halo, which was the first one, and I
said, use Higfield's marketing studio to
create a launch video. So Higsfield in
here has a really cool thing called
marketing studio where you drop in a
product or a link to a product and you
can even put in your own custom avatar
and it basically turns it into a
different type of format. So Hypermotion
sort of like this. It could be an
unboxing. You know, there's other
styles. There's UGC. There's so many
different things you can do in here for
marketing. Like these hypermotions are
super super cool. I mean look at that.
So I told it to use this marketing
studio format inside of Claude right
here. So, it looks at the marketing
studio. It found out what to do, and it
comes back with this.
As you can see, it's it's cool, but it's
not like the Hypermotion style. It's
very quiet. We have that weird scene
where the person kind of intimately
touches the headset. Don't know what
that's about, but it's [music] it's
fine, right? So, I said, "Okay, that's a
little bit, you know, not what we want.
I want you to use the Hypermotion
variant, and I want you to make it more
engaging, and I also want a 16x9
version." So, I wanted it to capture
more attention. And then that's when it
comes back and it gives us this one,
which I absolutely love. I think this
one is really good. [music]
Okay. But then for the 16x9 version, it
said that it was sensitive content and
it refunded my credits. So I said,
"Okay, try again." It did the exact same
thing. And then eventually I was able to
say, "Okay, why did that get denied?
Show me the prompt. Figure out why that
happened." It read me the prompt and
then it said, "Okay, I think it's
because of these words, you know, all
this kind of stuff. So I'm going to get
rid of that." And it does it again. And
then I was able to get this version
which you guys also saw in the intro of
this video.
So it's not perfect, but what we're able
to do is we're able to build skills and
stuff around this so that this doesn't
happen again where we're getting
sensitive content blocks. Okay. So
another quick example, I drop in an
image. So let's say we already have a
product that we want to start with. I
want some advertisements and stuff for
that. So I ask it to, you know, make me
a couple of Instagram ready ads for this
product and if it has any questions to
ask. So, it asked me one thing and I
gave it a quick answer and then it
starts generating some stuff. So, here's
one picture. Now, what you'll notice is
it got rid of some of the words. So, on
the original photo, we had like some
extra little captions and subtext right
here, and it got rid of that. So, we
have to be more specific about telling
it to not change the reference image at
all. That's very important. But anyways,
that's a nice picture. This one's also
cool. It's a little bit more of like a
effects type of picture. And then we
also have this one which is kind of like
an Instagram story which isn't exactly
what I was looking for but it does look
good as far as like the interface and
the realism. So it said, "Hey, we have a
calm one, we have a cinematic one, and
we have like a real relatable one." So
now we're able to keep iterating with
what we want. But I said that's not good
enough. I need these to be actual ready
to go advertisements across different
socials. And then it comes back, it
generates some more for us. So this one
has text. It says, "Stop counting sheep.
Start sleeping through the night." It
has sort of that cinematic feel. That
one I thought was pretty cool. We also
have this one which I loved. Asleep in
10 minutes, fall asleep faster, stay
asleep longer, wake up refreshed. I
absolutely loved this one as well. And
you can see with very minimal prompting,
all I said was, "Hey, create me
Instagram ready ads." It understands
like headlines and spacing. And I just
thought that these looked really, really
good. And then we had one more down here
as well. So the main problem is that it
didn't have the bottle appearing exactly
as we wanted it to in the reference
image, which is a pretty easy fix. So
here's another one. You guys didn't see
this yet because it's a lot slower paced
and it's not the exact like hypermotion
style, but it's still a nice little
animation. And then we also have this
one which is just, you know, the person
kind of looking at it. So, these are
decent videos, but they're not ready to
go ads. So, we had to be a little bit
more specific again. So, I said, "Give
me one that's fast-paced and energetic.
It has camera cuts. It has slow motion.
It has close-ups." And then we got the
one which you guys saw earlier, which
was right down here. It took me a few
more tries. And then we got this one
that you guys saw in the demo with the
capsules. I thought this one was really,
really good. So, what's cool about this
is you're able to take a super vague,
highle idea. You can say words like
engaging, cool, fast-paced, things that
are emotional, and Claude does the hard
work of figuring out the prompting, and
then sends that over to Higsfield
Marketing Studio, which has a nice like
pre-trained model in the back end. And
then you get stuff like this in minutes.
And then what you're able to do is you
can say, "Hey, this one was a winning
ad. You know, this format, this style,
this color way. I want a bunch of
different versions of this to test out.
And it will just go through and it will
plan out and strategize on the different
versions, the different headers, and
then we'll just go make all of them. And
now you have so many more pieces to to
test. And ultimately, once you find your
winning combo, you just chuck more
budget at that one and really try to
scale your product. Okay, so that's how
you do it in Claude. You use the
Higsfield MCP. It's super easy. It's
great to get some PC done in there. Now,
there's a lot of things that we want to
improve. The image stuff, we want more
control. We want to build some reusable
skills. We want to build some
automations and that's where we're going
to head from Claude into Claude code.
Now, don't get scared. We're going to be
using the desktop app just for today's
tutorial and all this looks like is
Claude. You have a chat and you have a
project and you're able to build way
more power in this interface. So, I'm
going to show you guys how. So, the
first thing you're going to want to do
is you're going to want to open up a
blank folder. You're going to go to your
Finder wherever you want to have it. So,
wherever you want to have this, you
could just have it right in your
desktop. You're going to create a new
folder and call that like Higsfield
Marketing Studio or whatever you want to
call it. So, in my case, this is called
Higsfield Studio. So, the very first
thing that we need to do is get
everything set up. So, let me show you
guys the way that I would prompt this to
get set up. I would go into Higsfield.
I'm going to click on MCP and CLI. And
when we're specifically doing this for
Claude or if we want to do this with
OpenClaw or Hermes or whatever, we want
to do this with the CLI instead of the
MCP. Now, the reason being ultimately
functionally they can do pretty much the
same things, but the MCP has all those
tools. So, from a token perspective,
it's actually more expensive to use an
MCP. And the CLI is just better for
agents. It's going to be faster. It's
going to be more efficient. Like I said,
we're going to use the CLI. So, all you
have to do is copy these three commands
exactly. I'm going to copy this. I'm
going to copy this. And I'm going to
copy this.
And I'm going to go into claude code and
say this project is basically being set
up to use Higsfield and it's going to be
set up for kind of a creative studio, a
marketing studio. I need you to install
the Higsfield CLI. I need you to then
run the O for me to sign in and then I
need you to install the Higsfield agent
skills. So here below are the three
commands. And there you go. I paste in
all three commands and then I just go
ahead and run that and it's going to get
you set up. It's going to install the
CLI and then it's going to do the O
flow. So, it'll open up a tab and then
you will just sign in wherever you
created your Higsfield account and then
it will add the agent skills for you to
use. Now, here for me specifically, when
it tries to install this, it's going to
say, "Hey, this already exists." But
yours will actually just go ahead and
get set up. So, here you go. It says the
CLI is working now running off login,
which opens up a browser. And as you can
see right here, it's basically just
asking me if I'm okay to connect Claude
to Hicksfield. And you're going to go
ahead and hit connect and then sign in.
And now you have been authorized. And
back in Claude, it should say, "Okay,
cool. You're now connected in. I can see
your account." And now I'm installing
the agent skills. So exactly like you
see right here. Now while this is
getting set up, there is something I
want to talk to you guys about, which is
the fact that this stuff isn't magic.
This stuff just lets you automate things
and ideulate. So my point being, if
you're not a master copywriter or
advertiser, it might be really tough for
you to build amazing tier one
advertisement copy and creatives. And
that's why what you can do with Claude
is you can utilize other people's
expertise and you can bring that in to
make Claude code the subject matter
expert here. So it's not perfect. You
know a master copywriter is going to
build a better newsletter automation
than I would. So what you can do is in
your project you can do some research.
So here's a chat that I did earlier
right before this. And I basically said,
"Hey, I need you to do a deep research
on the best strategies for advertising
in 2026 when it comes to organic
advertisements on platforms like Tik
Tok, Meta or X, and what captures
people's attention, what converts, and
how it differs per platform." So, I
basically wanted it to create a full
markdown file called advertising
masterclass that would live in this
project. And then I could have my agents
look at that when they need help
ideulating or when they need help
analyzing what's going on with our data.
and it's going to help them give us
better copy and give us better prompts
to feed into Higsfield. And this is
something that I do all the time
whenever I'm building different agents
or automations. I always leverage
Twitter threads, YouTube videos,
perplexity research. I utilize
information that's out there and proven
and I bring that into my systems. So
basically, this did all that research.
It asked me questions and then it gave
me a full markdown file which now lives
in this project. As you can see,
advertising masterclass.mmd. It's 617
lines. I could go ahead and open it up
right here and we could read this which
is a master playbook for organic
content. It's last updated May 2026. We
have a cheat sheet. We have different
platforms and we have a bunch of
information about how attention is
captured. And now all of our
advertisements are going to hopefully be
better because we've done a research doc
like this. But anyways, now we have the
CLI installed. We have been
authenticated in and we have our skills
installed. So we're ready to get started
trying to build some automations here.
Okay, so I cleared out that chat and
here's the first thing that I would
recommend you do. So in my Higs field,
if you guys remember, if I go to my
assets, we already have a ton of assets
generated. We have 45 different assets
created. We have a few different
products. We have a sleep pill thing. We
have a few different headphones that
were generated, a few different UGC ads.
So here's what I want to do.
Go ahead and take a look at all the
assets that we've generated in
Higsfield. I need help basically
creating a log tracker of every
generation that we do together just for,
you know, um visibility into our prompts
and our data and statistics and things
like that. And I want you to formulate
this into a Google sheet. Um a few tabs
if you need, but use the GWS CLI in
order to create this Google sheet and
organize it based on, you know, like the
product and the, you know, the prompts.
Maybe however you think that this makes
sense. Ultimately, this project is being
set up to become a master creative
agency. So, we need to have a database
where everything lives so that we can
track stuff over time as we scale up how
many pieces of creative media we have.
So, the reason why I want to do this is
because I ultimately want to get to a
place where we have something like this
as an example. So, I have all my
generations here. We can see the
product, we can see the style, we can
see the image or video, the model, and
we can see what we're actually
generating. We can also look at the
results and we can look at the actual
prompts for all of them which is really
important. From there we can analyze
which ones of these do we like the best?
Which ones actually converted the best?
Which ones, you know, had the best
budget or had the best spend on our meta
account or whatever it is. And we can
have all these other statistics like by
product, by style. We can have some
planning and then based on all this data
and especially if you bring in actual
real data from your Google ads or your
meta ads or even just your Tik Tok or
Instagram account, Claude Code can look
at it. It can use the subject matter
expertise that you had at research and
then it can plan things. So now it's
planning out different versions of ads
based on certain things. So we have
different value props, different
headlines, different avatars, different
styles, and it gives us this test matrix
where we now have a hundred different
things to test and they all switch up
little different variables and we can
ultimately test way more things now
because we're not the bottleneck on
creativity and we're also not the
bottleneck on production because I could
set an agent off to generate all this
stuff and then I could go to bed and I
could wake up with a hundred different
ad copies and creatives ready to go. And
then you could also have an agent that
every single week generates 100 more. So
you just have like this unlimited bank
of things to test and it's all based on
data, not just random stuff. So it was
looking at the master sheet which
already exists, which is this one right
here. So I'm just basically going to go
ahead and say, "Hey, I actually just
want to create a completely new one.
That one was um good, but I'm just doing
a demo, so I want you to just do it
again so I can show my audience how good
you are at things like that."
And if you guys haven't used the GWS CLI
before, it's amazing. It's another CLI
just like this Higsfield CLI is a CLI
and our agents are now able to super
quickly look at Google Sheets, Google
Docs, Gmail, Calendar, Drive. It can
look everywhere and it's much much more
efficient than using like a bunch of MCP
servers or a bunch of API calls. So, if
you haven't tested out the GWCI before,
it's a huge unlock. I'll drop a full
video right up here where I talk about
it more. Okay, so now it has pulled all
45 of those generations as you can see.
Let me just open up this sheet so we can
take a look at it. We've got all the
generations right here. I'm going to go
ahead and make these smaller. Okay, so
we've got these 45 generations. We can
also see by product. We can see by style
and planning. So really what I wanted to
do there is just show you guys that
Cloud Code can now look inside of
Higsfield, see everything that we've
done, and not only just see it, but it
can pull information like the job ID,
the status, the prompt, you know, the
sizing, all this kind of stuff. That's
really important. I mean, think about
how long this would have taken you to
manually go look at all your stuff and
get it into some sort of internal
database. And then, of course, this is
where it's able to build on top of it,
and it's able to give us tons and tons
of new ideas to actually go and generate
more creatives from. So, let's actually
go ahead and do that. I'm going to open
back up Cloud Code, and real quick, I'm
going to do an at sign, which is going
to let us tag certain things. And I'm
going to tag the advertising
masterclass.mmd file, which is, you
know, the full breakdown. And I'm going
to say, "All right, so I want you to
look at all of the different generations
that we've done. I also want you to read
that advertising masterclass doc, and I
want you to help me figure out a bunch
of different variations that we could
create. You know, we've done some things
with different headers, with different
styles, with different types of content.
And I want to mix and match a bunch of
different variables so we can ultimately
test a bunch of these and put a bunch of
budget behind this and see which one of
them spends the best. So use your
creativity here. use your best practices
and help me get a bunch of different
ideas for, you know, more creatives.
And once we shoot it off with that plan,
I probably should have said to put that
into the GW CLI into that Google sheet.
Hopefully, it understands that. If it
doesn't seem like it's understanding
that, I'll go ahead and stop it and say,
"By the way, put that in the Google
sheet." But that is what we're looking
for here as a deliverable. Okay, so it
looks like this is all finished up. I
did have to end up telling it to put it
in the Google sheet. Wasn't that smart
yet, but let me go over to the sheet and
we'll see. We have this new tab called
creative slate. And here, this one looks
better than the previous one. It didn't
give us 100. We could obviously say,
hey, give us 100, but this one ended up
giving us somewhere in the 30. So, it
also kind of showed us priorities. So,
these obviously need to go ASAP. And
then we've got other ones as well for
different products. You can see the
Murmur Halo, we've got the sleep
supplement. So, anyways, but now we have
this database that we can look at. We
could also have some sort of status so
that when we are having it automatically
generate these, it can mark them off as
processed or done or whatever it is. And
then it will create the prompts and talk
to Higsfield to create them for us. So,
it's going to be very, very cool. Sorry
about the lighting. I just saw like
apparently a tornado came through and it
got very dark. So, I turned on my little
light. Okay. So, now that we have all of
these examples set up, let's say that we
want to generate these top five priority
ones. So, rows three through 7 we're
going to generate. So what I want you to
do is now create the prompts for rows 3
through 7. So those first five that you
created. But what we also need to do
which is really important is we need
tracking. I noticed on the sheet you
didn't have any status column. So add a
status column. And what I want you to do
is create the prompts for those five. Go
off to Higsfield and generate them and
then mark them off on the sheet once
they come back and they're done as
complete or in review or whatever you
want to do there. Just mark them off so
we can keep track of what's going on.
So, just shut that off. If you guys are
curious about how I'm talking with my
voice, then check out the tool in the
description. It's called Glido. I
officially have joined the Glido team,
and I'm super super excited about it.
I've switched over from Whisper to
Glido. I just truly believe in the
vision that we're building over here.
So, if you guys want to support, and if
you need a voice tool, check out Glido.
It's faster, it's private, and it is
going to be way more agentic. So, join
the movement. But anyways, this is going
to shoot off to Higsfield, and I'll
check in with you guys when we get those
advertisements back to take a look at.
Okay, so those five are finished. I'm
going to go into the actual Google sheet
so we can take a look. We can see over
here that it's added a status column.
It's marked these as complete. We have
the result URL. We have the job ID. So,
let's take a look at just a few of these
real quick. Okay, so this one is
interesting. It's sort of like a meme.
You know, it's 18 months no sleep. So,
there's that. You can also notice that
the image doesn't really look like our
reference image at all. If you guys
remember, if I come over here, it was
this one. No, not this one. Sorry. It
was this one. So, that's honestly my
fault. I didn't prompt it to do so. So,
we're going to have to redo another
round. But let's real quick just see
what else we've got here. Because what
you'll notice is these probably aren't
going to be super consistent. And that's
because we're just kind of blindly
prompting. We're pulling the lever on
the slot machine, which is AI. And if we
don't have guidelines, if we don't have
recipes around it, skills, then they're
not going to be super consistent. So
this one, I don't know what that is. Um,
this one, this is a video,
[music]
very generic. Okay. So, what happened is
in the prompt, I'm assuming it basically
said, "Hey, it is a blue bottle. It says
sleep support on it." And that's it. So,
it's creating these just random looking
sleep support looking bottles. So, what
I'm going to do is I'm going to have to
go back into Cloud Code. I'm going to
drag in the actual image. This is our
actual product image. This is an asset
that we should always be using. So, when
you're creating these advertisements for
the sleep supplement product, it has to
appear as shown in this reference image
every single time. It must appear
exactly like this. Same color, same
text. Don't change anything. And I need
you to go ahead and regenerate those
five examples. Also, remember the goal
here is conversion. The goal is to get
someone to want to buy our product. So,
go ahead and do those five again. Now,
obviously, we're looking for some sort
of consistency, but what's important is
we have a different kind of angle. You
know, this one was curiosity, this one
was contrarian, this one was a pattern
interrupt, a question, and a stat flash.
So, that's the value of being able to
generate so many different types of um
angles, but also what you'll notice here
is it used different models. It wanted
to try these two with Nano Banana 2. It
wanted to try these two with GBT image
2. So, we just have a lot more to play
with here, and it's obviously way more
automated. So, I'll check in with you
guys when we get those back. So, I
thought while this was running, and
apologies if you hear thunder or fire
trucks. I wasn't kidding about the
tornado. Um, I thought that I would take
a quick second to talk about skills
because what happened here is one of
them came back with um being restricted
just like we saw earlier. And so, what
we can do is start to build a bit of a
knowledge bank around what prompts get
restricted and why and what don't so
that it doesn't happen in the future.
So, what is a skill? A skill is
essentially a recipe for an AI agent. So
if someone said, "Hey, can you make me
some chocolate chip pancakes?" You would
pull up a recipe of chocolate chip
pancakes. And you would make it and then
next time you would pull up that same
recipe and you would make the pancakes
and they'd be the exact same. But if you
didn't have a recipe and you were kind
of guessing the measurements and
guessing the order and the temperature,
your pancakes would come out different
every single time. So when we give our
agent a skill, it basically means, okay,
whenever I want an Instagram ad, you do
it exactly like this. And now everything
feels on brand, everything feels
consistent. So if we bake into a skill,
hey by the way, in the past you used
these five phrases and these five words
and it got, you know, basically flagged.
So don't ever use those five words or
phrases ever again. And the coolest part
about skills is every single time that
you run your skill, that skill gets
better because you can run your skill
and you can say, "Okay, you just created
me these five advertisements with this
skill. I don't like X, Y, and Z, but I
love A, B, and C. So update the skill to
make sure that next time, you know, it's
better." So, while this is actually
finishing up and while those generations
are happening, let me just show you
something. I'm opening up a new chat in
this project and I'm going to go to our
clot over here. Let's say that we want
to find one that we really, really like.
So, actually, one of my favorite
generations so far was this one. What I
can do is I can take this prompt and I
can copy this prompt. And essentially,
what I'm going to do is reverse engineer
a skill from this prompt. So, I'm going
to go back into the claude. I'm going to
paste in that prompt and I'm just going
to start yapping.
Hey Claude. So this prompt that you're
looking at right above is my favorite
output we've gotten from Higsfield
Marketing Studio. This was a hyper
motion fast-paced kind of like launch
video for our product and I loved it. It
had fast cuts. It had nice zooms. It had
nice details. And I want to turn this
into a skill that lives locally inside
of this project in the do.cloud/skills
cloud/skills
so that anytime I ask for a hypermotion
style video, you will utilize this and
they're always consistent and they
always have this style. So, turn this
into a skill for me.
And that's basically it. I mean,
obviously, this skill is not going to be
perfect on the first shot, but when it
comes to actually creating the skill,
that's all it takes. And usually the way
that I like to build them is I like to
play around with a bunch of outputs. you
know, maybe generate five different
things and then I pick the one that I
like the most or the two or three I like
the most and say, okay, how can I
reverse engineer a skill from these
outputs? And that's exactly what you
just saw me do. Okay, so these should be
done. Now, I'm going to open up the
sheet and we're going to take a look
hopefully. Now, the most important thing
I'm really looking for here is that the
images or sorry, the picture of our
product looks exactly as it should. So,
perfect. This one looks exactly like the
reference image. This says 18 months no
sleep, then seven nights of this. Try it
tonight. a 60 night money back
guarantee. And this looks like an
Instagram story style ad. According to
the research that it did, this one is
kind of what happens and what should be
converting. Let's take a look at this
next one. Here we have the sleep bottle,
which looks exactly as it should, which
is perfect. It says, "Melatonin does not
equal sleep. Try the formula. 28,000
parents swear by free shipping." So,
once again, this looks like it's
supposed to be sort of an Instagram um
story style of advertisement. Let's take
a look at the video we've got here.
Okay, so super short 5second video. I
don't love this one. I don't know if
it's super engaging, but hey, this was
based on the research that our agent
did, and obviously we would test this
one. If it's not spending well, we would
kill it. This one is more of a square
style. So, it's looks like it's only one
out of five different carousel slides,
but why am I exhausted at 2 p.m. even
when I sleep 8 hours? Advanced sleep
formula. Tap to see why. Okay, so that
was just really proof of the bottles
actually coming through now as they
should. This one has a huge stat up top.
So we can see that all of these were
based on the on-screen text, based on
the CTA, based on the platform fit and
the notes and all of this other stuff
that the agent did research on and
helped us ideulate on. Now what I want
to do is let's try to make another one
based on this skill. So once this skill
has finished up, we will try to invoke
it and we will try to create another um
hyper motion style video from this skill
right here. All right. So, it created us
one called Hypermotion video. Now, keep
in mind when we installed our um
Higfield CLI, we also installed the
agent skills. So, even if you don't have
this one and you say, "Hey, can you
grant me an image? Can you grant me a
video?" It should automatically be
triggering these other default Higsfield
skills automatically. But anyways, what
we're going to do is we need to open up
a new session to try to use this skill.
Okay. Now, before I actually use the
skill, I want to check did it save our
reference image or not. So, I'm going to
go back into this. I'm going to click on
files and I want to see if we have any
brand assets. It doesn't look like we
do. We have a bunch of data. Actually,
wait, no, we do. Right here, data
assets. We have our sleep bottle image.
So, you can't see it in this preview.
But if I actually open up our folder,
which this project lives in, which is
right here, our Higsfield studio. If I
go into data and if I go into assets,
you can see that it did upload this as a
reference image, which is great because
what that means is in a new chat, I can
tag it. So, it was called sleep bottle
reference PNG. So, I can use that and
then I can hopefully do a slash command
for Higsfield. Oh, no. It wasn't called
Higsfield. It was called hypermotion.
So, if I do slashhypermotion. Okay, I'm
not seeing it right now. Let's try to
just invoke it by natural language. So,
I want you to use the hypermotion skill
and turn this sleep bottle image, which
is the reference image I've tagged, and
I want you to create a Hypermotion style
video in Higsfield using their marketing
studio.
So, that's all I'm going to say for a
prompt. I'm not going to give it
anything else. What I'm watching for
here is to make sure that it actually
invokes the skill because every time
Claude code invokes a skill, it will
tell you that it does. So hopefully what
we see is that it's searching for one
and that it actually calls it. If it
doesn't, I'm going to stop this
generation. And right now it's running
the wrong skill. It's running Higsfield
generate. So this isn't the one we
actually wanted to do. We wanted it to
run the hyperotion skill. So what's
happening is probably just because we
just created that, so it hasn't
registered yet. So I'm going to go ahead
and stop this session real quick. And
what we want to do is check if that
skill actually exists. So, I'm going to
go to our project. I'm going to go back
to the main section. The skills will
live in acloud folder. So, skills
hypermotion video. The skill does indeed
exist. So, I'm not exactly sure why it
didn't get called. Let's open it up real
quick and take a look at it. This is
what a skill file actually looks like.
It's just marked down. It's called
Hypermotion video. Generate a
Hypermotion style premium product launch
video via Higsfield Marketing Studio.
High energy. When to invoke, what to do,
what to ask before generating. basically
the template. So, here are the hard
rules for the skill. So, I might just
have to like close out of the cloud app,
open it back up, and then we should be
able to see the skill. All right, so I
close out of the app and now that I'm
back in, I can see the hypermotion video
skill. And I'm just going to say this is
the skill that I want you to actually
use.
I also realized that my dictation
accidentally corrected hypermotion to
remotion. So, that's why maybe Claude
got a little bit confused, but it's
going to look at the image. It's going
to read the skill and then we should
have a pretty solid output. And because
it read the skill, it said, "Okay, one
quick question before I lock in the
prompt. Do you want a model in the ad?
Do you want it to be UGC or do you just
want it to be product only?" And I'm
going to say product only. And hopefully
it should be good to go now. All right.
So, moment of truth. This is done. I'm
going to go ahead and open it up. Let's
see what we got.
Wow. I mean, that's crazy good. I think,
you know, obviously this is where I'm
like, "Okay, that's pretty bad." But all
of this stuff, I mean, like, it followed
the skill and we'd be able to say, "Hey,
I like this. I don't like this." And
make it a little bit better. But I think
that this is really good. I mean, I
really liked the feel. It looks very
real and yeah, I am pretty happy with
this output. Now, it is a little bit
unfortunate because in the reference
image, all of the words do come through
perfect. So, it's not an issue with the
reference image. It's an issue with the
model that generated this video.
Sometimes models are going to mess up
text a little bit, especially when
you're doing image to video rather than
image to image. Now, one thing to keep
in mind is this is the worst that AI
video generation models will ever be.
every day, every month, they're going to
get better and better. So, right now is
the worst it'll ever be. But, I do
wonder if there's some stuff that you
could do in that video and in the
prompting of the video to actually make
it a little bit more accurate. And I
think if it were me and I had that
output and I just, you know, was getting
that sort of quality, but the words
weren't coming through right, then I
would probably just say, you know what,
that's fine. For our videos that are
this high quality, we're just going to
use a different label cover, which is
just the logo and the name rather than
like all the little metadata that we
might not need right now. So anyways,
there are some ways to work around.
There's some ways to have a better
positive attitude about it rather than
just hating on it and calling everything
AI slob. And because this was using
marketing studio video, it said that it
didn't actually use specifically one
model. It kind of used a mix because it
used, you know, marketing studio. So you
don't choose it directly unless you
would have ran it with some sort of
flag. So anyways, this is kind of the
main workflow, right? We're using it to
ID8. We're filling in a sheet. We're
marking off statuses. But how do we
actually start to actually automate
this? Well, think about this. In Claude,
we're able to set up these things called
routines. And what routines are is it
basically just on a set cadence injects
a prompt into claude code. So what we
just did here, this could be a routine.
All we have to do is prompt it to do so.
So, in a routine, what we could do is we
could build a new one that basically
says, "Okay, every Sunday, I want you to
look at this Google sheet and I want you
to also pull in data from, you know,
Instagram or wherever we're posting this
stuff. And I want you to analyze what's
working, what's not, and then I want you
to ideulate and I want you to add on top
of the sheet 50 new generations." So, 50
new every single week. And then what we
do is that let's say that that's a
Sunday night. We could maybe have a
Monday morning one. That's a new
routine. Okay, Monday morning, you're
going to go to the sheet and you're
going to pick 30 videos with a blank
status. And that's how we ensure that
we're not duplicating efforts. So, let's
say it picks, you know, these 30. It's
not 30, but let's say it picks all of
these because there's no actual status.
It would grab all 30 of these. It would
create the prompts for all of them. It
would generate all of them, and then
we'd wake up on Monday morning with all
of these completed with URLs and with
job IDs. And then we could scale it up.
Maybe we're doing planning every Sunday
and Thursday. And then maybe we're doing
generating every Monday and Friday. And
maybe we're scaling up from 50 to 100 or
200. And that's how you sort of push the
system to the point where it's scaling
way faster than you could as a human or
even maybe multiple humans. And then if
you want to take it one step further,
you could actually connect this pipeline
once you actually get it in a place
where you trust the outputs to something
like potato or even maybe plug it into
the meta ads manager and you're starting
to schedule and post these things
automatically too because you've built
up a batch of skills that you actually
trust enough to just let them run
autonomously. So that's kind of the idea
and everyone's going to get in here and
everyone's going to do it a little bit
differently. But it's really really
simple to set up your routines right in
here or to come into here and say, "Hey,
I want you to set up a routine for me 8
a.m. Monday. Do this and this." because
it's all very possible with natural
language. So, if you guys want to dive a
little bit deeper into routines, I'll
tag a full video right here where I dive
into how you set them up and some of the
little gotchas that are in there. But,
that is going to do it for this video.
So, if you guys enjoyed, please give it
a like. Helps me out a ton. And as
always, I appreciate you guys making it
to the end of the video. And I will see
you in the next one. Thanks everyone.