It has never been so easy to build
whatever you want. And so in today's
video, I'm going to show you guys how
easy it is to build a voice agent with
just your natural language using Cloud
Code with 11 Labs. So, let me show you
guys a quick example. I had this crazy
idea where I was thinking, okay, I've
got a ton of YouTube videos, exactly 400
actually, and all of these YouTube
videos, there's a lot of different
tools. There's a lot of different things
that I've mentioned, and some people in
my audience might be confused and might
want to just have a nice way to like
chat with those YouTube videos. So my
crazy idea was, okay, what if I just
built a voice agent that people could
talk to and it had been trained on all
of my YouTube transcripts ever. And so
that's exactly what I was able to build
in about 15 minutes. I told Cloud Code
the idea and it figured out how to do
everything. Pull the transcripts,
connect to 11 Labs, put this on my
website, and just prompt everything and
build the tools that it needed. So let
me show you guys a quick demo. I'm going
to hit start call on this website and
then start the call. Hey, I'm Nate's AI
trained on his YouTube content. Ask me
anything about Claude Code agents or
what he's been building.
Hey, I'm curious. What are probably like
the best scraping tools that Nate might
have talked about on his channel.
Give me one sec while I look that up.
Nate talks a lot about Firecrawl as a
powerful scraping tool. It's super
versatile and can do things like scrape
entire web pages, map out a site's
architecture, crawl through different
pages, and even search the web to turn
pages into structured data. He often
uses it with cloud code through an MCP
server to automate these tasks.
Okay, so let's say I wanted to build my
first workflow ever in cloud code. What
would be maybe a good use case that I
could use firecrawl with to build some
sort of automation?
That's a great question. A fantastic
first workflow would be to scrape job
listings from a website and put them
into a structured format like an Excel
sheet. Nate has shown how firecrol can
easily grab all the job details from
multiple pages and claude code can then
organize that data for you. It's a
practical way to see the power of
firecraw and agentic workflows in
action. Okay, so I'm going to go ahead
and end that conversation, but what you
guys basically just saw there is I was
able to get all of the YouTube
transcript knowledge into this voice
agent and then I'm able to just talk to
it and it seamlessly fits in right here
on my website. So if anyone comes here,
they would be able to actually start a
call and talk to it. It's not actually
going to be live. I'm going to take this
down, but this was just for the demo
because if you've ever built a voice
agent before with without using cloud
code, it's a lot of manual configuration
because you go into the 11 Labs
platform, you've got your agent right
here and you have to manually configure
the system prompt. You have to create
the first message for the knowledge
base. Do you want to drop this in as
just a document or do you want to give
it different tools and you want to have
it be able to query like you know a
subbase vector store or pine cone vector
store or maybe even notebook LM like how
do you want all the data to come
together at the end of the day? But now
just by brainstorming with cloud code
and giving it some sort of you know
highlevel idea it will go ahead and do
the research and figure out the best
method for you and then it will go ahead
and build a voice agent in 11 Labs and
configure it all up. So that's exactly
what we're going to do today as a live
demo with cloud code and 11 Labs. So
before we get into the live demo, let's
just actually talk about what's going on
with a voice agent. So it is a loop.
It's not magic. So a visitor let's say
comes to a website calls the AI agent
and the agent listens through your
microphone. The LLM on the back end is
able to get that message, transcribe it
into text, read it, and then either come
back with the next message or read the
database or, you know, hit some sort of
tool call and then come back to the end
user with some sort of answer, and then
the loop pretty much just runs again.
Now, there are four kind of main pieces
inside of every voice agent. We have the
persona, which is basically the system
prompt. So, if I go back into my 11 Labs
dashboard, this system prompts right
here where we're saying, "Hey, you're
Nate's AI assistant. You are on his
website. you have information about all
this. This is the persona. We could tell
it to be rude. We could tell it to be,
you know, conversational like Nate
himself. We could tell it to tell jokes
after every single sentence and it would
do so. And that is us basically setting
the persona of our voice agent. Then we
also have the voice. So you can pick
from all the different voices. If I go
over here to creative and I go to I
guess we could have done it on the other
side, but voices, you can see there's a
bunch of voices. There's trending
voices. There's different ones like
iconic voices. And you guys might have
noticed that that one sounded like me.
What I did is I used my actual
professional voice clone which is
trained on like 4 hours of my voice. And
then we have knowledge. So this is where
you know you would give your agent
information about your business or
information about you know the customer
database or whatever it needs. Whether
that is something that it can
communicate to the client. So for in my
example, YouTube transcript data or
maybe this agent is a customer support
agent and it needs to be able to look up
someone's order and then tell them, you
know, like the status of it. So there's
different ways to give it knowledge, but
that's an essential part of a voice
agent. And then you also have tools,
which we would go ahead and configure in
your 11 Labs voice agents. So for
example, with this assistant that we
were just looking at, if I go to tools,
you can see there is a tool right here
that says list GitHub repos, but there's
tons of different tools you can add. You
could add an MCP server. You could have
it do a direct basically API call. You
could even have your 11 Labs agent call
on, you know, a tool that you've already
built, an NN or a Python script or a
Zapier automation. Whatever it is, your
agent should be able to actually call
it. And you don't have to set this up
manually. You know, normally you'd come
in here and you'd add a tool and you'd
have to configure everything. But Cloud
Code reads the 11 Labs documentation,
understands everything about 11 Labs
agents, and then just does it all for
you. So those are the four pieces. Code
beats clicks. basically just validating
that it's so much better to just build a
voice agent by speaking into your
computer rather than going onto the
dashboard and clicking and clicking and
saving and maybe forgetting to save
things and maybe making a mistake with
the endpoints or something. But all we
have to do now is just talk to Claude.
So there are three different ways
typically to think about a voice agent.
You can either do it in the dashboard.
So if I come over here and if I was
building this agent, I could test it. So
if I go zoom out a little bit, we could
test the agent and talk to it right
here. The other way is we could embed
that into a website. So, as you guys saw
here, there's a little button to start a
call and that would trigger our AI
agent. So, that's kind of called a
website widget and then you could also
hook this up to a phone. So, you could
connect your Twilio, you could pair that
voice agent that we're building with a
phone number and then you could have
that voice agent either call people from
that number or if someone calls that
number, the voice agent would pick up.
So, those are the three main ways. Today
we're going to be specifically looking
at the embed, but there's multiple ways
that you can actually build and connect
voice agents. And the funny thing about
the widget, and it's not too funny, but
it's kind of cool, is it's literally
just one little block. If you see here,
I click on the widget tab. All it says
is, okay, add the following snippet to
the pages where you want the
conversation widget to be. And I would
just copy this, give it to Cloud Code,
and say, hey, put this onto my website.
It's as simple as that. So, with all
that out of the way, let's go ahead and
just jump into a real quick live build
of a voice agent. Okay, so the first
thing that we're going to do is we're
going to open up Claude Code. Now, you
could use this in the desktop app like
you're seeing right here. I personally
don't love using the desktop app. I
actually prefer to use VS Code, which is
just an ID. It's completely free to
download. Just go to Google, search
Visual Studio Code, and download that.
And then when you open it up, it should
look something like this. What you're
going to want to do is open up a
project. So, open up a blank project on
your desktop or your documents or
wherever. and then open that up in here.
You can see what I have right now is
just a very simple project and all we've
done in here is we've built a website or
a simple landing page. So, this is my
simple landing page here. It is for an
AI kind of like consultancy or
transformation partner and I had Claude
just spin this up because this is where
we're going to be embedding our voice
agent widget in today's example. If you
don't already have a website, then don't
worry, you don't need one. You can still
follow along and you'll still be able to
build a voice agent. It's just that I
want to show you guys how you can
actually get that embedded at the end of
the tutorial. So, we're in this project.
We are going to open up Cloud Code. So,
I'm basically just going to click on
this little button right here in the top
right, which opens up Cloud Code. Now,
if this is your first time in VS Code,
what you're going to have to do is go
over to the extensions right here. Click
on that, search for Claude Code, and
then go ahead and install Claude Code.
This will basically allow you to open up
the little extension. Now, once you
install this, it's going to prompt you
to log in. You have to have a paid
account of uh Claude in order to access
Cloud Code. So, sign up for your
subscription and then log in right here.
And then you'll open up Cloud Code like
this. Now, here's where I said it gets
pretty cool because all I have to do is
come down to the bottom right, click on
plan mode, which basically means that
Cloud is going to help us think through
what we want. And as humans, we're very
good at knowing the end goal, but we
don't always know the way to get there,
right? So, all I have to do is speak to
it, and it's going to help ask me
questions and guide us in the right way.
So, hey Cloud Code, what I've got for
you is a bit of a project. So, I have a
website which is called Neural. It is
inside of this project and it's
basically just our landing page. We run
an AI consultancy and this is our
landing page. And what I want to do is I
want to embed a voice agent widget onto
my website. I want this agent to have
information about the business. I want
it to be able to answer questions from,
you know, prospective clients. But
ultimately what I wanted to do is try to
push people to book in a discovery call.
That's kind of your job. So you're kind
of like a salesperson, a sales agent on
my website. So what I want you to do is
help me figure out how do I embed you
onto the website? I want to use 11 Labs
and then how do I actually prompt you in
the right way to, you know, be a
salesperson. And then how do I actually
connect you to cal.com, which is where
I'm using kind of like my booking. It's
synced to my calendar. So, it should
show people available slots. And how can
I give you access to that tool so that
you can actually just go ahead and book
meetings for people? They would give you
like maybe their email and their full
name and then you would just go ahead
and use the cowl.com tool and book a
call for them. So, that's kind of the
highle goal that I have for you. Help me
figure out the best way to do this and
ask me any questions that you have if I
didn't explain anything clear enough.
So, that is the prompt that we're going
to send off. If you guys are curious
about how I was able to dictate and the
text appears, then check out the link in
the description. It is an amazing tool
and it's changed the way that I work.
And by the way, you may notice that
currently I'm using Whisper and I'm
actually pointing people towards GLO.
GLO is much faster. It's private. I
fully switched over, but Windows support
is coming in like a week or so. So
that's why right now you're seeing
Whisper. But that's why I've officially
joined the GLO team because the product
is truly so much better. Anyways, like I
said, this is going to go ahead and
start brainstorming. If you want to
check out the superpowers skill, it's
also completely free. Um, just go to
Google and search Claude Code
Superpowers and you'll have to download
that. But it's super easy and I like to
use it for brainstorming. But now I'm
just going to check in with you guys if
it comes back with any questions so I
can show you the way that we answer
those. All right, so here are some
questions that we have. What's the
current state of your 11 Labs setup?
Well, in 11 Labs, let's go to our agents
and let's just pretend that we don't
have any currently configured and we
want to build a new one. So, I would
basically just go into cloud code and I
would say nothing or I guess I would say
I have an account but no agent yet.
Cal.com, what's the current state of
your cal.com setup? I have an account
and event type ready. Yep, that's
exactly what we've got. How do you want
the agent to actually create the cal.com
booking direct from 11labs to cal.com?
That's what I want to do. You could,
like I said earlier, have 11labs call an
end workflow and the end workflow books
the event, but that's just too many
pieces. So, we're going to go straight
from 11labs to cal.com and I'm going to
shoot off those answers. And so, just in
case you guys are curious, cal.com is
basically like the same thing as
Kalanley. It syncs to your Google
calendar or, you know, your Microsoft
calendar, whatever you want it to be,
and it'll show people available slots
they can book in. So, we can actually
give our 11 Labs agent access to this
and it can just book in calls for people
instead of having us have to do that
manually. We got some more questions
here. So, how should the widget appear
on the page? Default floating bubble.
That's perfect. What voice persona do
you want for the agent? We're just going
to go with a warm, professional B2B
sales tone. That's perfect. And data
fields beyond full name and email, which
are required to book. What should the
agent capture during the conversation?
Company name would be great. The problem
they're trying to solve would be great.
Team size and ro, that would also be
great. And if there's anything else I
want, I could just go ahead and add
other and I could type more. But for
now, I'm good with those three things.
So hopefully you guys see the value so
far. It's going to do all the research.
It's going to figure out how to make
these two tools talk to each other or I
guess three technically and it's going
to ask me all the questions that I need
to make this agent behave the way that I
actually want it to. All right. So, what
happens now is it comes back with a plan
for us to review. So, neural voice sales
agent pluscow.com booking. It's going to
give us some context and it's going to
show us the architecture of what it's
actually setting up. So, let's see what
it's going to do. It's going to first of
all do some cow.com prep. So, we're
going to have to go get our API key and
we're going to have to give it to Cloud
Code. So it can actually, you know, do
that. And then we're going to have to
give it the ID of the actual event type
that we want it to use. If you guys
remember back in Cal, we had a few
different events. So we probably want to
give it the ID for this 30inut event.
And then it's going to have to make sure
that there's proper authentication
between 11Labs and Cal.com. Hopefully
it's able to take care of all of that
for us. And then it's going to go ahead
and build the agent. It's going to pick
a voice. It's going to pick an LLM. It's
going to set up the first message. It's
going to system prompt it. It's going to
do all of that for us. And then it's
going to configure the tools. And it
looks like there's going to be two. It
has to add one to check availability and
then it has to add one to actually book
in a call. So that's great. It's going
to take care of all that. Here is the
system prompt that it's actually already
drafted up, which is fine for now. And
then the last step will be to wire the
widget into the site. So that's what
we've got. I'm going to go ahead and go
back to the main conversation and I'm
just going to go ahead and accept those
edits because all of that looks good to
me. And by the way, you guys might be
wondering why am I using 11 Labs over
some of the other things out there.
Well, I have my voice clone in 11 Labs
and I think it's the best professional
voice clone you can get. I also really
do like the interface. As much as we
want to stay in cloud code, when I come
into 11 Labs, I just feel like I know
where everything is and I like the way
that it all works and it makes it super
easy with that widget embed. So, that's
why I'm using 11 Labs in today's video.
And if you want to check out 11 Labs,
just go ahead and click that link in the
description and it'll send you right
over here. And at this point, I'm going
to put this agent in bypass permissions
mode so it can just go ahead and start
banging out this plan. But it looks like
it wants something real quick. The order
of operations matters here. Steps one
through six are all dashboard work incin
cal.com and 11 labs that only you can
do. We could actually have it do it if
we gave it like computer use. But
anyways, step seven, the only code
change needs your agent ID before I can
make it useful. All right. So tell me
exactly what you need for me. If you
need API keys, then create av file and
I'll drop everything in there. But just
walk me through step by step. What do
you actually need from me right now? I
want it to make my job as easy as
possible. Okay. Okay, it's kind of
funny. It wanted me to go do everything.
So I said, "Hey, I want you to do
everything. So, you know, figure it
out." And now it comes back and says,
"Okay, you're right. I actually can do a
lot of this. So here's what I need from
you." You can see it's created av file
and we need to go get our cal API key
and our 11 Labs API key. So let's go
ahead and do that real quick and let it
know that that job has been done. So
first I'm going to go to Cal and I'm
going to go to my settings and I'm going
to click on API keys down here at the
bottom and I'm going to create a new
key. This is going to be called demo.
I'm going to delete this later, so I
don't really care. And I'm going to
create that, copy this, and then go back
into cloud code. And if I click on thev,
it created these placeholders for us. So
all I have to do is paste in that API
key, hit control S, and that is now
saved. And now for 11 Labs, I go back
into my 11Labs dashboard, and I come
into my settings, and I go to
developers. You can see there's an API
keys tab here as well. I can go ahead
and create this key. Call this one demo.
and go ahead and create that key.
However, I didn't select any
permissions. So, it says you're creating
an API key with no permissions, so it
won't be able to do anything. So, what
you have to do is give it access to
things. Or I could just turn off the
restricting. So, basically saying, hey,
this key can do anything, which is fine
for this sake. And you could also set a
monthly sort of like spend limit, which
is pretty cool. But I'm going to go
ahead and create that key. I'm going to
copy this API key, go back into Cloud
Code, paste that in there, hit CR S to
save it, and then I can close out of
that. And now that we have those two
things configured, cloud code, I just
dropped in those API keys. Keep going.
And now you can see that it's going to
just move its way through this to-do
list. It'll pause and it will ask us for
something if it needs us. But hopefully
it should be able to knock out most of
these without our input because we took
the time and effort already to explain
what we want and align on the plan
before we started to let it actually go
build anything. All right, so just a few
minutes later, apparently everything is
live. We have been verified into
calendar. It's going to use the 30
minute slot which is fine. And it's also
suggesting that we rename that call
neural diagnostic because right now in
our calendar it is just called like 30
minute call or something like that.
Yeah, it's just called 30-minute
meeting. So it's telling us it's using
this one and it wants us to rename that
which is a good tip. It also created an
11 Labs agent. So if I go into my
dashboard here for the agents and I
click on agents right here we see neural
diagnostics. So, this is the one that it
just built with a full system prompt.
And if I click on tools, we should see
that we have two tools set up, which is
awesome. We haven't yet tested them.
We're going to have to see if they work,
but everything looks like it has
actually been configured. So, it's
saying that this is now live on the
site, at least the local host version,
and it wants us to test it. So, let's go
ahead and open up the site. Give this a
hard refresh. And right there in the
bottom, you can see that we have this
widget. So, I'm going to click on start
call, and let's just test this thing
out. Hey, what's going on?
Hey, just here to answer any questions
about Neural or what we do. Are you
looking into AI automation for your team
or did something specific catch your
eye?
>> Okay, so I went ahead and ended that
call because I don't love that voice. It
was Adam and I just didn't like the way
he was speaking. Also, for some reason,
the first message didn't come through.
So, I clicked on the button and then I
had to just wait and I was like, "Okay,
why isn't it speaking?" And then I had
to start talking and then it came back.
So, at this point, what you're going to
do is you're going to keep iterating.
You know, it's not going to be perfect
on the first try. So, I'm going to go
back into this. I'm going to do a real
quick session handoff, which basically
is just going to give us a message to
clear the context and put the message
back in just because I want to keep my
context clean so it's able to, you know,
we don't get into context rock territory
or anything like that. This is basically
a skill I built to just give me a
summary of where we're at, what's
important to remember. If you guys want
to check that out, join my free school
community. All my skills and all my
resources are in there. Okay, so we just
tested out the agent on the site and it
looks good. It works for the most part.
Okay, a couple things I noticed. First
of all, change the voice. I don't like
this voice. It sounds a bit too
enthusiastic. It sounds too AI. The
second thing is when I click on start a
call, it doesn't actually give me a
first message. For some reason, it makes
me start the conversation. Even though
in the dashboard, it looks like you did
configure a first message, but we're not
actually getting that to come through.
So, I haven't yet tested out the tools,
but I just wanted to make these quick
changes to the actual prompt. Um, so
yeah, go ahead and implement those
changes, and then I'll go ahead and test
it again. And it's really that simple.
You iterate by saying, "Hey, here's what
I liked. Here's what I didn't like. Go
figure it out for me." So, it's really
having trouble with that first message
thing. And it's funny because on my
other site in this one, when I did this,
it one-shotted the the first message. It
had no issues. Maybe it's something
going on behind the scenes. But, you
know, I don't want to be the one to have
to dig through the documentation to
figure that out. So, I'm having it do
that research. It's going to look up
everything that it needs to find out in
order to fix this. So hopefully I'll
check in with you guys in just a second
and this issue will be fixed. But that's
just an important mindset thing to go
through here is because cloud code has
the ability to reason and do research.
If something isn't working, be specific
about what's not working and you know
give it context, but it's going to be
able to go do the research to figure out
how to troubleshoot that specific issue.
>> Hey, this is Nurl. What brought you in
today?
>> Hey Nurl, I was wondering if I could
book a call.
Got it. Just to clarify, today is April
28th, 2026 and it's currently about 7:55
p.m. UTC, which is around 2:55 p.m.
>> Okay, so that was better, right? um we
need to change some things because it
was getting the current time wrong and
also we need to prompt it better to
actually understand that it needs to
confirm how you spell people's names and
how you spell their emails because it
wasn't formatting the emails right. So
every single time that you talk to this
thing, you're probably going to notice a
few things that you need to improve on.
So I'm basically just going to give it
that feedback same way I told you guys
what's missing and then we'll test it
again and we'll hopefully see that it's
better. Now the other thing you're going
to have to pay attention to when it
comes to availability is your actual
booking. So whether you do that on
Calendarly or Cal.com, the booking has a
certain sort of like limit. So if I come
in here and I go to availability, you
can see it's only going to give me
availability between 9:00 a.m. and 5:00
p.m. on weekdays. So if I wanted to be
able to change this, I would have to
edit that availability. So let's just
say for the sake of the demo, we're just
going to say that we're available from
9:00 a.m. to 900 p.m. And I'm just going
to copy these times throughout the
entire week, like I said, just for the
sake of the demo. And we're going to go
ahead and save that. Okay, so I've got
it making some changes here. It's going
to speak only in central time zone
because that's what I'm in. It's going
to speak a little bit more concise,
which I just wanted it to speak more
concise. It's also going to validate
that it's spelling back the name and the
email correctly because obviously it has
to have the email correct in order to
book the correct type of appointment. It
moved the temperature down a little bit
just to make the outputs a little bit
more um consistent. And I think it was
because I asked it to make it more
concise. And then it also made sure the
tools were working. So, what I ended up
doing is saying, "Hey, I don't like it
spelling it out, NATO phonetics, because
it was it was just taking too long." So,
I also have it making that change. And
once that has gone through, which looks
like it is now through, we're going to
go back into the app. I'm going to give
it another hard refresh. And let's try
one more time to do a booking. And
hopefully at this point, we would be
like, "Okay, cool. We like this agent."
So, I'm going to give it a call.
>> Hey, this is Nurl. What brought you in
today?
>> Hey, Nurl. I own a construction company,
500 employees. We're looking to automate
our proposal generation. It's very
manual and I want to book a call with
your team. Like I said, I'm the the
founder and the owner of this company
called Sandbox Construction.
>> Got it. Want me to grab the minutes on
the team's calendar? It's a fit or no
fit call. No pressure. They'll listen to
what you're running and tell you
straight whether we can help.
>> Yeah, let's go ahead and grab a a time.
Can you let me know what slots are
available for today?
>> Sure. What's your full name and what
time zone are you in?
>> My name is Nate Herk, spelled H E R K.
I'm in central time zone.
>> Let me confirm. Nate, Nate. H E R K.
Herk. Did I get that right?
>> Yep, that's right.
>> Great. And what's your work email? Spell
it out character by character for me.
Let me confirm. N A T E H E R
K88gmail.com.
Did I get that right?
>> Yep.
Perfect. And what specifically are you
trying to solve with the proposal
generation? What's manual about it
today?
>> Yeah, we're basically just handwriting
all the proposals and we're also quoting
everything manually. So, I want to have,
you know, AI be able to help us with
taking raw requirements and turning that
into a proposal that we can just shoot
off to our clients.
>> Got that. And what's the size of the
team handling proposals right now? Or
what's your role in the process?
The team is 500 people and my role is
just I kind of oversee it.
>> I've got one slot left today, 6:30 p.m.
Central. Does that work?
>> Yeah, I mean that works, but I would
love to be able to do, you know, 7:30
p.m. Central. Is that not available?
>> Not showing anything at 7:30 p.m. today.
Want me to check tomorrow or another day
this week?
>> Okay. So, what we notice here is the
flow is working a little bit better.
Honestly, I think it's asking me too
many questions because it's making it a
little bit tough to demo, but
um there should be open slots. You can
see the calendar is open from like 400
p.m. all the way to 9:00 p.m., which if
we go back to our calendar event, we
should have availability all the way
from 9:00 a.m. to 9:00 p.m. So, what I
want to do is I want to figure out why
is the calendar tool not working the way
it should be. So, I'm going to go ahead
and do another session handoff. I'm
going to clear the context so we can ask
Cloud Code to help us debug this issue.
So, this is what I said. I said, "I need
you to help me figure out what's going
on with the tool call because the check
availability tool just said, "Hey, we
only have 6:30 p.m. available, but we
should see 4 p.m. all the way to 9:00
p.m." So, there's a couple things that
could be going wrong here, right?
Cal.com could be returning only 6:30,
which would be something's wrong on
Cal.com. Or the agent's not using the
tool correctly, and maybe it's only
querying a very limited scope. or
cal.com returns several slots but the
agent is misreading the output. So
there's basically three different pieces
or three different areas where something
could be going wrong and we need to
figure out which one of those happened
so we can fix it. You know we could come
into our actual dashboard and we could
click on tools and we could look at this
endpoint and we could figure out what's
going on. And what else is cool is we
can see all of the actual conversations
we've had. So we can track all these
what times they were. we can actually
listen to them as well and read the
transcript and that is what helps us
have more visibility in order to debug
and optimize these over time. Okay, so
apparently the agent found the issue. So
there's two problems. One of them is a
real bug unfortunately. So turn 16 in
the transcript, we can see what actually
happened with the check availability and
the agent constructed this as UTC rather
than central time. So the search window
was off. So what it needs to do is
change the actual parameter in order to
be querying at the right spot and then
hopefully we should be able to fix that.
There is another observation that the
system prompt says to just read back two
or three slots. But that's not really
the main issue. The main issue was that
the actual tool call was being conducted
wrong. So while this is fixing it, let's
just go back to the dashboard and talk
about how we got there. Right? We could
have either manually came in here and
inspected everything and tried to figure
it out. But did you guys see how easy it
was for cloud code to find that? and all
I had to do is explain my experience,
what I experienced that went wrong. Now,
some of you guys may have heard that
demo and you might be curious about like
the latency and stuff, that's where
you'd want to come in here and play
around with different models and
different prompting. And I've also
noticed when I'm testing this on a
website with a local host, it's just the
latency is a little bit worse than when
it's actually kind of like a live
widget. So, keep that in mind. But
there's other things that you can do. If
you guys remember here, we were
basically seeing the live transcript.
And if you don't like that, you don't
have to have that. That's just something
that my cloud code here added in. But
when you come to the widget, you can
configure a lot of different things with
the interface. You can change the color.
You can see that send text while on
call. You can have a real-time
transcript. There's lots of things that
you can do when you configure this
actual widget. Like I said, it can be a
different image if you want. It can be a
different color. Lots of things you can
do here. Okay. So, anyways, what broke?
We just saw what broke. And now,
apparently this is fixed. So, we're
going to do another hard refresh and
we're going to try to fly through
another demo because this this dude Nurl
really likes to yap. But let's see if
that's fixed.
>> Hey, this is Nurl. What brought you in
today?
>> Okay, I don't want you to ask me any
questions. I just want you to book a
call for me. Just right now, please book
a call. My name is Nate Herk. My email
is nateherk88gmail.com.
nat h rk88gmail.com.
And I want availability for tonight. I
need to get something in urgently. Just
please don't ask me questions and let me
book a call.
I have tonight at 6:30 p.m. 700 p.m.
7:30 p.m. 8:00 p.m. or 8:30 p.m.
Central. Which works for you?
>> Let's go ahead and do 700 p.m. Central.
>> You're all set for 700 p.m. Central
tonight. You'll get a confirmation email
at nateherk88@gmail.com
with the video link.
>> Okay, so that actually worked. You can
see that that was completely debugged.
And the reason you guys might be
wondering like why was 4:30 or 5 not
available? Well, I'm assuming that was
in Cal. So, if I come into Cal and I go
to um limits, there's probably something
right here. Minimum notice is 2 hours.
So, if right now is 4:30, it's going to
make the first available slot 6:30
because that's 2 hours later. So, that
worked perfectly. It found the right
availability and it booked in this um
meeting with the right email as you can
see. And also in my nate
herk88@gmail.com,
I just got this notification. So this
would have accurately sent an email to
any client that booked a call right in
here. So that all worked perfect.
There's obviously some things that I
don't love about the prompting and about
maybe the appearance. And this is where
you would start to sort of iterate on
that kind of stuff, but from a technical
perspective, this worked as expected.
The tools are working. You know, the
creation is working. And that is what is
the most important for the sake of this
demo was me showing you guys how we got
that set up without me having to go read
any API documentation or do anything
manually inside of this actual agents
configuration in 11labs. And now what
you would do at this point is you would
basically just publish that website. So
I'm not going to go over that in today's
video, but all you'd have to do is sync
this website to a GitHub URL or GitHub
repo and then you would sync that GitHub
repo with Forcell. So I've made multiple
videos where I've gone over this. I will
tag one of those right up here if you
guys want to see that process, but it's
super simple. So now let's talk about
who pays because there's definitely some
things that you want to be considered of
when you put a widget on your website.
That widget is synced with your 11 Labs
account. So every time someone talks to
it, you are going to be eating that
cost. Unless of course you have some
sort of authentication or it's an app
and they put in their API key, then it's
obviously going to charge them. But if
you just leave that on your website and
someone has really malicious intent and
just talks to it for 24 hours a day,
that is going to come back and eat your
credit. So that's something you want to
think about. So there's things that you
can do when it comes to security. So one
of them is just locking the host name,
right? This widget can only appear on
nate.com, not anywhere else. In case
someone inspected the code, stole that
HTML widget, which is very doable, you
know, cuz the widget is basically just
this. If someone stole this and put it
on their site, boom, they have a voice
agent that's that's yours. So you could
come into security and you could lock it
down by domain. So you could add the
host for an allow list. And also, I
believe in the widget, there's settings
down here for um allow domains right
here. And once again, yes, you can do it
in here, but you can also say, "Hey,
cloud code, help me lock this down. I
don't want people to abuse this."
There's some other things to think about
as well. So, knowledgebased grounding,
feed the agent real docs, otherwise it's
just going to make up things, right? The
conversation cap. So, maybe you want to
set a max duration ceiling per call. So,
that's kind of like a budget guard rail
or maybe, you know, like a max minute.
Or maybe if you wanted to get really
technical, you would have to have people
authorize in in order to make a call.
You could also set up a rate limit. So
if the page is public, throttle just to
make sure that the widget isn't being
abused a thousand times per second by
the internet. And then like I said about
latency earlier, if you're using a
premium voice with a really smart LLM,
there's just going to be more latency,
and that's just how it works. So figure
out the tradeoff that you [snorts] want
on your website. And once again, now
that you've set up this voice agent, you
could use it wherever you want. So what
we just showed off was having it on a
website like this, for example, but now
that we have this agent, we have the
tools configured, we have the prompting
configured, we have the the voice, the
personality, we have everything set up,
we could also just hook this up to a
phone. So not only could people come to
Neural and talk to our agent right here,
but if we hook this up to a phone, a
phone number, then if they call Neural,
then we could also have the agent pick
up. So that's what makes this thing
pretty powerful. It's the same engine
behind the scenes. It's just a different
door. So, that's what I wanted to share
with you guys today. Hopefully, you saw,
you know, we iterated maybe four or five
times and this took me, you know, maybe
45 minutes to do this demo for you guys.
But, think about if you spent 5 hours
sitting down testing this thing and just
iterating and just using your natural
language. By the end of the day, you
would have a really solid voice agent
ready to go and you didn't have to deal
with any of those headaches of API
documentation or, you know, configuring
things together manually. We built it in
code. We now could push that with one
command. We could embed that on a real
domain. And then we would have to talk
and brainstorm with cloud code about how
do we lock this down? How do we make
this safe? How do we make sure we're not
going to blow through a thousand credits
overnight. There's lots of different
ways to do it. It all depends on your
specific scenario. So, that is going to
do it for today. I hope you guys enjoyed
the video. If you did or you learned
something new, please give it a like. It
helps me out a ton. And as always, I
appreciate you guys making it to the end
of the video. I will see you on the next
one. Thanks everyone.