If you've been feeling overwhelmed
trying to keep up with the different AI
tools and agents and different things
that you should be using, then this
video is for you because there's a lot
in the space moves really quick. So, I
want to show you guys the tools that I'm
actually using on the day-to-day and the
tools that I use every once in a while
and talk about why. I'm also going to
talk about my mindset when I'm living in
this environment, experimenting with new
stuff, and what actually moves the
needle so that you guys don't end up
getting in the cycle where every single
month you feel overwhelmed because
there's so much new stuff to learn. All
right, so let's just go ahead and get
started. This is not a technical
breakdown of all these tools. This is
just my list and me personally telling
you guys about the tech stack that I use
and why. So, we're going to start off up
top with our S tier. These are our daily
drivers. So, you know I have to chuck
CloudCode in there. This is probably my
overall number one favorite AI tool
ever. This is basically my operating
system. I live inside of my CloudCode
project and I try to do as much work as
I can directly from inside of CloudCode.
Now, up next on the S tier is VS Code,
which is basically where I like to use
my CloudCode. You could use it in the
desktop app, straight in the CLI. I like
to use it inside of VS Code, which is
just an IDE, meaning you could also use
CloudCode inside of different IDEs like
Cursor or, you know, Winzer for
anti-gravity. So, here's VS Code. I can
see my files on the left. I can have
CloudCode in the terminal right here or
I can use the CloudCode extension. And
our third and actually our final S tier
AI tool is Glydo. This is our
speech-to-text startup and I fully
transitioned over from Whisper to Glydo.
It's the fastest one on the market. It's
private and we're going to make this
thing super agentic. So, if you want to
check it out, link in the description.
And Windows support is literally about
to roll out. So, stay tuned for that.
Okay, so now let's move on to A tier.
Now, these are the ones that I'm using
on a weekly basis 100% but they're not
really my daily drivers. So, the first
one we have is Codex. Codex is a similar
type of agent hardest to CloudCode and
I've been using it a lot more lately
because a lot of its strengths
complement CloudCode's weaknesses and
vice versa. So, they're really good to
be able to use together even though
right now I still do the majority of my
work inside of CloudCode. And by the
way, if you guys are seeing some tools
throughout and you're curious and you
want to see more about how I use them
or, you know, better breakdowns, then
let me know in the comments what else
you guys want to see. The next A-tier is
just Claude in general, Claude chat.
Now, typically I am using Claude code
for all of my chat-based stuff, but I
still do have some times when I just go
to chat really quick because I can just
open it up and it's right there and I,
you know, chat. Okay, the next one,
which I have not talked about too much
on this channel at all, is Hermes agent.
I've been using this a lot more lately
and it's really nice for general
knowledge work and being able to do
stuff when I'm out and about because it
wakes up on demand when you talk to it
through Telegram. It has instant crons.
It has a lot of things that I really
like about it that are just easier to
set up sometimes than doing a whole
Claude code infrastructure setup. All
right, next we have Perplexity. Now,
Perplexity I feel like isn't as popular
as, you know, it used to be. I I don't
really use Perplexity computer too much,
but when I am plugging in automations
and I'm having my agents do research, I
really like to use Perplexity for my
research. I'm also using Groq a lot as
far as research and, you know, using X's
built-in Groq right there when I need
to, you know, maybe I want to search
through a lot of Twitter threads or
something and I want to find specific
posts or find specific insights, I like
to use Groq in X for that. And so,
that's honestly my core stack. That's
all we have for S and A-tier. And the
reason I wanted to show you guys this is
because it's a pretty lean stack. When
it comes to core AI tools, it's
basically Claude code, Glido, Codex,
Hermes agent, Perplexity, and Groq. And
you can see how many tools there are
still down here to be placed into
different categories. Now, I don't want
to get into a bunch of like different
project management tools and like things
like, you know, Hostinger obviously is
my VPS provider for Claude code or for
Hermes or for other things that I'm
setting up. You know, ClickUp is where I
live as far as project management and
stuff like that and communication with
my team. Fireflies is in all of my
meetings and, you know, I just wanted to
chuck these in here to give them some
love to show you where they fit in my AI
stack, but these aren't really ones that
are like my AI first tools that I'm
using on the day-to-day for knowledge
work. So, the specialists are one where
I use them for a very specific use case,
you know, like I have a certain process
that I need or within processes I have a
very specific task and then I would go
grab some of these specialists. So,
another example would be Appify. I don't
live in Appify, but every once in a
while I'll have an automation or every
once in a while I want my Hermes agent
to grab something and it has to use
Apify and a certain actor within Apify.
We also have things like GBT image 2,
which I've been loving lately, and Nano
Banana 2. They're really good at
different things. I kind of use Nano
Banana as like my Photoshop tool and I
use GBT 2 as like my creator tool, if
that makes sense when it comes to
images. And then usually when I'm
plugging in like image generation or
video generation into agents, I always
use key.ai for that. It's kind of like
the open router but for image and video
models. And then actually reminds me, I
left Open Router out of this, but Open
Router definitely deserves a spot in the
B tier for specialists. I've got a few
other specialists here and it's probably
going to shoot off the edge, so let me
just expand this a little bit. But I
also use HeyGen for whenever I need
avatars. I don't avatar my YouTube
channel and yeah, I know you guys say
that in the comments. I've never done
that and I don't plan on it, but I will
use this sometimes for certain videos.
Maybe for certain course material or
whatever it is, sometimes I will use an
avatar and I go to HeyGen for that. And
then alongside that, I use Eleven Labs
to clone my voice or for specific voice
agent builds. Okay, so it's really
starting to slim down here as you guys
can see. We only have one actual row
left, which is experimenting, but I'll
tell you what, not all of these tools
are going to fit into this row. So let's
see what's going to happen. Okay, so for
C tier, these are things that I'm kind
of keeping my eye on and I'm playing
with a little bit and I use very
frequently and they're in my ecosystem,
but I wouldn't really consider them a
main tool I use. Actually, before we get
to that, I did leave out Cloud Design.
Cloud Design is definitely a specialist
and we've been adopting it more and more
as a team because now everyone on the
team can build landing pages using the
exact same design system. I know you
could have done it either way in Cloud
Code before, but it just makes it so
much easier to share designs, comment on
things. We've been loving Cloud Design
for specific use cases. Okay, so now
let's get into the experimenting AI
tools. So honestly, Gemini. Gemini and
Anti-Gravity, I just don't really use
very often. It's not part of my core
stack. I am using Nano Banana more than
I would go talk to Gemini 3 Pro or
something like that in the actual app.
The next one would be Ollama. I don't
run on local models, but I do use Ollama
to download stuff or maybe to even use
their cloud because I like to play
around with the open source models and
see what's happening. I like to keep
up-to-date and experiment. And then the
last one that I wanted to throw on this
list was Manifold. I really don't use it
too much, but every once in a while I'll
just open it up and test out some
things. I know you guys have been giving
me some comments about Manifold, but
yeah, I mean I think it's a great tool
and if you were maybe new to this AI
world and you started with Manifold, it
could potentially be your main, you
know, S-tier daily driver. But for me, I
just would prefer to use my Cloud Code.
And now you may be wondering what's
going on with all of these tools down
here. These are in a separate category
for me, which I would call graduated,
which means they used to be somewhere in
this top four tier list, but now I just
don't really use them anymore. So,
ChatGPT, regular chat, I've graduated.
Open Claw, I've graduated. I would say
that Hermes has kind of replaced Open
Claw for me. Cursor, I've graduated
from. Notebook LM, Poppy AI, Anytten,
and then WhisperFlow. And one thing I
want to say about these graduated tools
is that this doesn't mean that they are
trash. This just means that I no longer
use them. I feel like I've kind of moved
above them. And this could be for many
different reasons. Maybe it means that
they're a little bit outdated. Maybe it
means that they were got replaced. Like
in this case, WhisperFlow 1 million
percent has been replaced by Glido. So,
this one we can even just put off to the
side. But like Anytten, not a bad tool
at all. I just prefer now to build
automations in Cloud Code.
Poppy AI, not a bad tool at all. I just
realized that if I want to use Poppy's
functionality, I could do that better in
Cloud Code and it can be more customized
to me and cheaper.
So, sometimes these tools, you know,
like Notebook LM, they're all very, very
good tools, but what I've done is
instead of paying for them now, I
basically have extracted the features
that I like from them and I've worked
them into my own ecosystem because the
idea really is to keep your tech stack
lean. And I know this looks like a lot,
but really, the daily drivers is the
main ones that I use. I could use just
my Cloud Code and my Glido and just work
the whole day and be fine. And I really
wanted to make this video because I've
been considering making more content on
Codex and Hermes Agent and maybe a few
other things, but I don't want to
overwhelm you guys, which is why I've
been only on Claude Code for the past
like 3 months. I was trying to stay
consistent so that you guys could try
to, you know, keep learning one tool
consistently. And I really hope that I'm
not contributing to your overwhelm and
maybe your stress with all this AI stuff
going on. I'm trying to keep you guys
all educated, but I also am able to
realize that when you see a new video
from me every day, it does feel like you
need to watch them all and drown and you
feel a little bit overwhelmed. So, I'm
trying to help you guys out here. By the
way, guys, I know we're about to cover a
ton of information in this video, so I
broke all of this down into a free
resource guide. All these tools, all
these different frameworks and rules to
remember, and I put that inside of my
free school community. The link for that
is down in the description. Once again,
completely free. You join here, you go
to the classroom, you click on all
YouTube resources, and you'll be able to
download every resource that I've ever
dropped on YouTube for completely free.
So, hop in the community and let's get
back to the video. Thanks, guys. So,
let's talk about some other mindset
stuff. I've got a couple different key
points here that I wanted to hit on,
which will hopefully clear up a lot of
this stuff. So, the first thing is that
coding agents are just harnesses. These
images are kind of funny. It just made
this up. This was GPT image 2, by the
way. But, they're all different on the
surface, right? They've got different
harnesses, they might use different
models on the back end, they might have
different ways that they use their
skills, but they're all just harnesses.
They're all just AI that work inside
some sort of directory. So, if you have
your project with your Claude .md file
or your agent .md file and your scripts
and your skills and whatever, all of
your different agents can work on that
directory. So, I have my main operating
system, right? Like my main project
called Herc 2, and I have had Open
Claude and Hermes and Codex and Claude
Code all be able to work inside of that
directory. So, they can all do things
for me in there. And the lesson here is
to build directories like they're going
to outlive any tool because they will.
We don't know if Claude Code's going to
be king in a few months. We don't know
if Codex will be king in a few months.
We don't know if some random startup is
going to, you know, just take over
everything. But, what we do know is if
we're creating directories and we're
creating our projects and we're keeping
them clean and we're building in them,
that whatever AI is the new kid on the
block will be able to plug into it and
it will be just fine. The next thing I
want you guys to think about is what is
your North Star? Because it's probably
very different from my North Star. You
know, obviously I've got a bunch of
business goals with what we're building
out with AI Automation Society and our
certifications and our events, but my
North Star when it comes to YouTube is
test out every tool,
form my own opinions, and share with you
guys what I think is interesting to
know.
And so that North Star for me means I
test out a lot of stuff. I jump on
announcements. I have to experiment. And
that doesn't mean that you have to.
Because if your star is building a
business or a company that does X really
good, like what is the mission, then is
every single new hot framework or every
single new model or trending tool or
latest feature is that actually your
path to the North Star or is that just a
distraction? Like the number one mistake
that entrepreneurs make is they get
distracted and they try to do too much.
So really the idea would be, okay, I'm
just going to stay on this path. I'm
going to save links to YouTube videos
that Nate drops. I'm going to save these
Twitter threads for later and just kind
of remember that they're there. But I
don't need to actually go learn all of
these new features. Maybe I'll watch
Nate's, you know, 10-minute video, but
that doesn't mean I have to dedicate my
whole next day to learning and building
what he showed. There's a difference
between knowing the what and knowing the
how. And sometimes you only need to know
all the what's. You don't need to know
the how's. And I've got another point
which is kind of like the decision
framework and I'll touch on that in a
bit, but hopefully this alone will make
you guys think, "Wow, you know, there is
a lot of things that I've just
experimented with and I don't know why.
I don't even have a use case for that."
This next one is the 20% productivity
dip rule. So basically it's the idea
that every single time you make a switch
in your business, you are going to maybe
lose about 20% of your efficiency or,
you know, whatever metric you're
thinking about. You're going to take a
20% dip because change is change and it
can be hard sometimes. So what you have
to figure out is, if I'm going to make
this change and I'm going to guarantee
have some sort of dip in productivity,
is that dip going to ultimately take me
higher than where I would have been? As
you can see, the blue line is worth it
and the red line is not worth it. If the
dip only gets you back up to the same
green line, then that's also not worth
it. It wasn't worth the dip. So, if you
know that the dip will actually boost
you above and take your business, you
know, maybe break through a plateau or
push to another level that you couldn't
have reached before without that dip,
then that's how you know it's something
worth doing. Okay, then we have
productivity is needle moved per hour,
not hours worked. I fallen into this
trap. I think a lot of you guys in my
community have fallen into this trap as
well. You work a 12-hour day. You think,
"Damn, I was productive today." But,
what you don't realize is like, were
you? Because I could maybe sit down for
4 hours and be more productive than you
in 12 hours because I'm actually doing
everything that actually moves the
needle.
Rather than 12 hours of responding to a
bunch of threads, reading through
community posts, watching YouTube
videos, just like planning out a bunch
of stuff, but not actually doing
anything. So, this kind of relates back
to that North Star thing. Let's say
every day you sit down in the morning
and you say, "Okay, by the end of the
day, I want to achieve X." Every single
thing that you want to do that day
should be driving towards achieving X.
And then maybe once you've achieved X,
then you can spend some other time like
looking into some new features and
experimenting with some stuff. But,
productivity means that you're actually
doing things that are moving the needle
for you. Not how long did you work
today? Okay, so this one kind of goes
back to that first point about the fact
that all agents and agent harnesses are
just different harnesses and they all
work in your same stuff. Because the
mindset here, which is something that
I've been thinking a lot about. I've
been building out frameworks, we're
building a certification program, we're
doing all this, and our thinking is
basically what Jeff Bezos said.
Think about what will never change, not
what will change. And so, if you can
become tool agnostic in the way that you
work, that means, "Okay, let's say
Claude Coach shut down tomorrow. Are you
okay? Could you pick up Code X? Could
you pick up something else? Could you
keep working? Could you be okay?" And if
the answer is no, you might want to
think about things, right? Cuz like, if
you're one of those people where I mean,
I've been there,
Claude goes down. Like, the status page
is down, the API's throttled, you can't
use Claude. Are you just sitting there
like, "Oh my god, I can't work anymore.
I have to wait till it's back up."
Because if that happens, then you're
probably not in a great spot. You
probably want to be learning how to plug
in a few other things into your main
stack, into your main working directory.
And what you'll realize is that you have
overall job responsibilities or
functions or processes. And what happens
in a process is that it's basically
built up of a bunch of different mini
tasks. And usually the right question
isn't which tool is best, the right
question is for this specific task in
this specific context, which tool is
best. So here's a quick example, right?
Like let's say I'm making a YouTube
video. Maybe I use Perplexity for
research. Maybe I use Claude Code with a
skill and with knowledge about me to
help structure the video. And then maybe
I use Claude Chat for some reason to
actually write the script. And then I
use like GPT image 2 to create me that
thumbnail. And then I use Nano Banana to
to add a glowing effect or to just make
some stuff stand out. And then after I
do all that, maybe I drop it into
DaVinci Resolve or Adobe Premiere Pro
just to stamp it up and get it out the
door. So not every single step in a
process has to be AI, not every single
step in the process has to be the same
AI. Break things down into baby steps
and think about for this specific baby
step, what tools do I have in my list,
you know, all of these different tools
that we looked at earlier, which one of
these tools is going to be the best for
this little output that I need. And the
last thing here is basically the
decision framework. So this is what I
alluded to when I was talking about that
North Star and finding the path that
you're running on which is directly
leading towards that North Star. When a
new AI tool or feature drops or a
YouTube video from me drops, look at the
title,
click on the video,
understand what I'm talking about, and
ask yourself, does this video or does
this new feature solve a pain point for
me right now? Most of the time, the
answer will probably be no. And if the
answer is no, but you think the feature
is cool or the agent framework is cool
or whatever it is, then just save the
link so that you know, okay, later if I
do want to watch this, I know where it
is. If the answer is yes, then maybe it
makes sense to actually test it out. But
don't just spend like a month testing it
out. Try to test it out in a real
scenario, you know, like don't just test
it out with mock data. Try to test it
out with something that actually moves
the needle for you. Not in a way where
it would be risky, you know, like
sending out emails or restructuring a
whole database, but do something in your
actual working environment, so you have
real proof of if you like it or if you
don't, or if it actually solves a
problem or not. And then, at the end of
the week after you've used it, just ask
yourself, did this make sense? Did this
solve my pain point to the point where
I'm going to put this into my main, you
know, daily drivers or my main
companions of tech tools, or is it not?
Because if it didn't, then get rid of it
for now. And then, only later, if you
realize, okay, I'm working on my
business and I'm I'm hitting this pain
point every single day. Do I have any
features or agents in this list of like
other things that I need to look at? Do
any of these directly help me solve this
pain point? If the answer is yes, then
you reach for that tutorial, and then
you grab it, and then you learn it. Does
that make sense? Like, sometimes, as
you're walking down this path, you don't
want to jump to the right or to the left
to all these holes, but sometimes you
might actually run into a roadblock. And
the only thing that might get you over
that roadblock is to jump into one of
those holes, understand it, and then all
of a sudden the roadblock is easy to
just like walk through or jump over or
whatever. Okay, let me take a breath.
>> [laughter]
>> I was talking really fast in this video,
and I don't know, it's just something
that I'm passionate about and something
that I wanted to get off my chest,
because I feel like I've been answering
these questions a lot in the comments
and in my community, but I really,
really hope that this one gave you some
clarity. And once again, I use a bunch
of tools, and I've really, really tried
to only bring you guys like cloud code
content for the majority, because I
don't want to overwhelm, but please let
me know what other tools do you want to
see me cover? Especially anything in
here, especially some of these constant
companions that I am using a lot. What
do you want to see? Just let me know in
the comments. But anyways, that is going
to do it for today. So, if you guys
enjoyed the video or you learned
something new, please give it a like. It
helps me out a ton. And don't forget to
download that free resource guide, join
my free school community. All of my
resources are in there. And yeah, I
appreciate you guys making it to the end
of the video, and I'll see you in the
next one. Thanks, everyone.