You can now build beautiful videos,
websites, and images using Cloud Code
and the new Higfield 2, even if you've
never coded before. And in this video,
I'm going to show you exactly how to
build your own content operating system,
so you can build beautiful and animated
websites, videos, and images quickly
using one single app. Meaning, you can
turn your viewers into buyers faster
than your competitors. And if you're new
here, my name's Jack. I built this on my
last tech startup with a gazillion
customers. Now I'm building my own AI
businesses and I share here the stuff
that actually works. So if you haven't
already, grab that beautiful coffee and
let's dive straight in. Higfield reached
out and said, "Jack, we want you to do a
video on our new MCP." I was like, "This
is cool because I use Higsfield every
single day. I've got results like this
using Higsfield." So it's very cool to
do it. And what I found is it leads to a
content operating system that really
unlocks some cool stuff inside Claude,
which I'm going to show you inside this
video. And I've also seen Higsville
everywhere. I see Higsfield online now
more than my own mom. That's how crazy
this is getting. But what's the point of
this? The idea here is if we can connect
Claude code or chatb 5.5 to Higsfield,
we can effectively create this unlimited
content factory. And the idea is that we
have everything in one app. We're going
to be building ours inside codeex and we
can essentially use Hicksfield as our
content generation system. So let's see
what this actually looks like. You have
access to over 50 generation models. You
going to have one brain that runs it all
with one really cool workflow. And the
idea is we can use this to generate
websites, videos, images, audio,
animation in one place. So here's the
key thing is that the reason why is
we've got time and there's quality. So
effectively what we're going to do here
with cloud code is connect to every
generation engine. So the idea is we got
cool code in the middle but we need to
use different models for different
things and often times the flavor of the
day changes. Maybe one day it's chat GBT
image, the next it's N banana, maybe
it's this video model, that video model.
Effectively we connect cla code to a
system that has access to every model.
We can essentially do everything within
one location. So Gemini, Nana, Banana,
Flux, Mjourney, Sora V3, you name it.
Everything connects into Claude with one
super duper simple integration which is
very freaking cool. And you can see the
different image generations we've got.
We've got lots of video generation
obviously Higfield itself, Runway Gen 4,
Kia AI 11 Labs and a gazillion a
gargantillion more sitting behind it
also. And so the idea here with all
these image generation, video generation
and audio voice and music generation is
effectively the brain which we're going
to be using inside code. we're going to
be tagging in various different models
is essentially going to pick the best
item for us for the specific job without
having to have like a thousand different
integrations. And we can literally swap
that out the second that something
better drops. So we don't have to
re-engineer our entire workflow. And so
we can power in this Higsfield MCP into
different softwares codeex open core you
name it. And effectively this content
engine can power through everything that
we needed to. Now there are a million
different applications for this. But
what we're going to do is get a website.
We're going to actually add in a video
component to that without ever having to
leave the Claude Code ecosystem, which
is freaking crazy. Get a new project,
get Claude Code to build the website.
Claude can add the images to that
website, and then we can get Higsville
to animate it, and then we can actually
push it live all within Claude Code.
Well, before we can do that, the very
first thing that we have to do is
basically connect either Codeex or Cloud
Code, whatever our environment is, to
Higsfields directly. Now, the great news
is it is very very easy to install. As
you can see, it works on lots of
different platforms. So, you can pick
the different integration vertical here,
but honestly, you don't really need to
do a lot. So, now we're inside Codex. We
want to go ahead and connect to
Hicksfield. Now, here's the thing.
There's a couple of different ways we
can do this. The MCP, the CLI, the SC. I
would recommend the CLI. It is way
better. It's the one that I'm going to
be personally using. So, all we're going
to do is come over and select the CLI.
We are going to copy this. Now the cool
thing about using the command line
interface which just plugs directly into
it is whatever model we're using codeex
cla code any of these things they can
all draw on the same connection which is
why it's superior in my view. So I'm
going to say hey there dude dude is
important I want to go ahead and install
the Hicksfield CLI onto my laptop. Okay.
And then going to paste in all this
stuff here and then just let it rip and
do its thing. Now when we want to bring
in claude code to the table to do some
really cool website design what we can
do very easily actually is click this
thing here at the top which is toggle
terminal like so and as you'll see
claude code is down here to come down
here and there's another conversation I
was having about the exact same thing
and I just come down I click on claude
and as you can see literally Claude will
now appear for us so we can have those
conversations super duper easy and
they're very easy to shut down. If
you're new to this interface, here's my
full video showing pretty much the 99%
of stuff you need to know about CEX. You
can go check that out and I'll be
waiting for you here when you come back
or welcome back if you're back with us
now. So, look at this now. It's going
ahead and getting a CLI installed and
verifying everything for us. And by the
way, if you do want to go deep with claw
code, I've got this full master class
just launched on my community this week.
It's got everything from power systems,
memory systems, clawbar apps, building
anything, design systems, compliance,
and turn that into dollars. I'll put a
link down below in description. I highly
highly high. It's stuff I've never
covered on YouTube. So, if you want to
go deep on that and learn the kind of
expert stuff, I'll put that down there
for you down below. Now, what's really
cool is when this is connected, we can
effectively use it for anything we want
to. And we have the full arsenal of
media and content and video creation at
our disposal. And then just like this,
this screen pops up that says connect to
Higs full. We're going to say, you know
what, we're happy to do that. We're
happy to connect these two worlds
combined, which is awesome. Now, my
devices are authorized. If we come back
over, that should all be finalizing. And
it looks like it's done. Oh, best thing
to do actually is why don't we go ahead
and give it an example. So, I might give
it a prompt like this. Okay, I would
like to create for me a 16x9 jibli style
image of uh three English Springer
Spananiels. Um, and then bring that back
to me and go ahead and use the nano
banana 2 model, please. Beautiful. And
just like that, now we've got it. So,
you can actually see this image. So,
it's given us the image here. We're
going to click on this guy. It's too big
to view. So, if we click on open up, we
see this right now. And do we have
Spring of Spinals? We do in Jibli style.
That is freaking awesome. Now, we did
this with nano banana. You can within
codeex use GPT 2.0 for images which is
incredible. But one of the limitations
is that we can only really do one at a
time. If we use Higsfield, we can do
four or so. And also, if any model comes
out and happens to be better than chat
GBT, we can leverage that also. But
where this really shines is in its video
generation, the cord video. So, what
we're going to do actually now is build
a website together. And what we're going
to do to do this is we're going to tag
in Claude code. So what I want you to do
is close this down here. And I want you
to come over and grab the terminal by
clicking on this button here. And then
what we're going to do is essentially
give it this command to create Claude.
I'm just going to do dangerously skip
permissions, but you can just create
Claude. And now we have Claude here. And
I want you to basically create a
website. So I'm going to say this. Hey,
I would like you to create for me a
website for a web design agency that
sells websites and services to
businesses. And I want you to do that in
the style of Versel. Okay. Enter that
in. And then to supercharge that, I'm
actually going to come up to this repo
here, which is a design collective,
which has design systems from loads of
different businesses. Like Spotify, for
example. I open this up. This is the
entire Spotify design system. So, this
is just going to help it shortcut it and
make it wonderful designs. So, I'm going
to click on code. I'm going to click on
this. Come back over and say, I'd like
you to do this and just gain some
insights from the design systems inside
this repo. And then we're going to throw
that one in. And then the other repo, I
actually made this one here, which is
something called power design, which is
effectively is based on universal design
laws that apply to everything. It's
really freaking cool. So, I'll show you
what this looks like in practice. It
essentially just goes through
everything. So, you know, it talks about
attention economics, um, all the best
design principles that exist. So, this
was built for slides. I'll put a link on
screen for that one if you want to. I've
never seen results as good as that. It's
really freaking cool. So, what I'm going
to come ahead and do is come back over
to the design repo. And I'm actually
going to go ahead and copy this bad boy
by copying the code, coming back over,
and then I'm going to say, I would like
you to be inspired by the design
principles contained within this GitHub
repo. And then I'm going to come over
and just throw in that one there. And
then basically set Claude off on its
merry way. Now, you could do this within
codeex track above, but the reality is
that the best model on the planet right
now is actually Claude for design. So,
we're going to use the best model for
the very best thing. Beautiful. And when
that's complete, we can check out what
those websites look like. And I got two
versions for you. So, we can check it
out. I always recommend we do this. So,
this is version number one, built for
websites, uh, built for businesses that
ship. Really cool. We got trusted by,
and then we can see all of the colorful
logos. I think that's really freaking
cool. Three stages. So, again, we can
come down and pick the kind of designs
that we think is cool. I think this is
refreshingly simple and gorgeous.
Actually, to be fair, I'm really
impressed with this. Obviously, it's
leaning in our power design skill, which
I built, which is just like one
basically one view port, one point. This
is a very, very nice option. And then we
can add in our video. The second option
we got is this one here, websites that
ship. Slightly different vibe and feel,
which is cool. Again, we got the logos
there. A site for every part of your
funnel. And I wonder if this is this is
really freaking cool. I like this
feature. Come down. Build the basic
website from idea to life in 14 days.
Built on the modern web. I'm not a big
fan of these like cody graphicy things.
I think they're kind of overdone now.
And then we've got probably a bit more
color, you know, contrast. That'd be
good. And then we've got everything,
which is decent. I really like this.
This is a really nice touch and feature.
Ready to ship. Then we can just
basically get on. So we just picked the
website that we like after running it a
couple of times. And honestly, I quite
like the first one here. I think we just
have a couple of improvements. So I'm
going to basically increase the size of
this. And then what we're going to do is
actually add in a a sort of like a
video. So when you scroll, it kind of
like animates a little bit. So I think
what would be cool is maybe we have this
slightly on the left. Then on the right
hand side, we could just have a laptop
with a gorgeous website on it. So we're
going to come here now. I'm going to
create a beautiful uh prompt. So I'm
going to say something like, hey, I'd
like to create for me a image of a
MacBook that looks beautiful with a
gorgeous website showing on it. Uh I
want this to be ideally image
dimensions. Let's do 4x5. Uh and I want
it to look fantastic and it must have a
white background. I'm bordered with a
white background. Please give me four
different versions of this and use the
best image model available. And then
I'll just add in Hixill CLI just at the
end there so we can rock and roll and
make sense. And this right here is
really cool. So look at this. I'll use
the image gen workflow which is great.
Uh and what's cool here is picked Nano
Banana Pro because it's the right pick
because it supports 4x5 directly and
goes up to 4K while GPT image 2 in the
CLI does not expose 4V5 in the CLI that
is. But what's cool is I can get four
separate generations and bring that
down. Ordinarily what I would often do
is go into the Hixite, basically the
Hickfield app and I'd look at the four
images. Then I decide what I want to do,
then I'd reiterate and do various
different things. It's very convenient
to be able just to file this off um
within the actual app itself. Now, this
is really freaking cool because not only
has it gotten all all four things down
for us. So I can click on this and see
the images, not this one here, but what
this has actually done in codeex is
created a contact stream. So I can just
click on this, have a look, and it's
grabbed all the four images and said,
"Look, which of these four do you
prefer?" So I think number four here,
which is number three, the V3 software
is best. Then we can do some magic. So
I'm going to give it the following
prompt, which is this. Hey there, I'd
like to create for me an animation. So
my desired end goal here is that
basically as the user scrolls on our
website that the laptop evolves in some
way, shape or form. So could you for
example animate this laptop such that
you know as they scroll maybe like the
graphs and things like the laptop opens
up a little bit and does something
creative and interesting. Use the best
video generation model that you can for
that. And when that's done I'm going to
go ahead and integrate that into the
website. And then what I might also do
is just say this in parallel, I'd also
like to create for me four different
image versions of this end state such
that if the video doesn't look as good
as we want, we could actually play
around with the images as well. And I'm
going to send this one off. Now, what's
really cool, guys, is that you can
actually head over to Higsfield, click
on images here on the top left, or like
come down to image and create an image.
And you'll see this page here, which
effectively is what it's designing. So
anything that we build together through
you know codeex through cloud code is
visible here. So you can see these ones
and I think it looks really cool. So we
might say hey this looks fantastic.
Maybe we want to go ahead and use that
one or maybe you like this one. So you
can effectively just go and pick the
designs that you think are really
decent. And the exact same thing is true
of the video which is generating for us
right now in the background. And then
guys when it's ready you can actually
come over to Hickfield and check it out
if you want to. Of course this will all
be available for you down below in
codeex. I think this one is really crisp
and really nice and it came out better
than the straight video one. I think
that when you give it a certain
dimension like a 4v5 and ask it to do
like landscape you there can be some
crossover but what was really cool about
using the Higful CLI here is the fact
that it actually found the right model
that can take the right dimensions and
I'm super impressed with that. So then
all we would literally do now is say hey
there I love the 4x5 one the latest
video gen. What I'd love to do is to
integrate that into the website on the
right hand side. And in addition to
that, I'd like to make the H1 and the H2
larger. We're going to have that on the
left and then this laptop on the right
hand side. And what I would love you to
do is have a scrolling animation. So as
I scroll through the website, basically
this whole thing just kind of like um
you know unfolds as I go through the
website. And while it's working on
building that, I want to show you
another little hack that we can do with
Higfield and that's something called
characters. What you can basically do is
create a character by uploading stuff.
So you click on this current character
thing and you can drop like 20 images
up. We recommend at least 20 to get a
good scope of it. So you see this one I
did here for example. If I come back
over to characters I'm breaking up
thinking about it. I can see now there's
me with like nine photos. So less than
you'd expect. But if you click on
generate, you can generate in the app.
Or if you come back over to your
environment, for example, and I just
open new chat, I could say something
like, "Hey, using the nano banana 2
model, use the Hixfield CLI to do a
photo of Jack drinking a coffee working
at a laptop face on." And then we just
send that off. And what's cool is you
just reference your name, Jack, and it
knows that. So if you wanted to do
custom photos for LinkedIn or something,
you can do that now all within your
actual environment. What's cool here is
it's now going ahead using the CLI and
start generating that photo for us
directly and then guys it will pull up
the image you can click on it take a
look captures your identity one
interesting thing though is like you
want to make sure that you reference my
character ID just say hey it's like a
character that an avatar that I built
and what we can do is basically say
awesome and now I'm like to turn that
into a skill such that if I ever ask you
to create a character including named
Jack you're going to go ahead and use
this character within Hicksfield then
literally you'll have this skill.mds so
you can click on it and you can see that
basically I've got the entire skill
here. So whenever I actually ask it
questions it will now build that and
that's how you build these content
systems is you find any use case you
want to for video image audio and then
when you're happy with the output we
just say hey turn that into a skill and
then we can use it whenever we want to.
Then after you've gone back with chat
GPT or if you want to chat with Claude
for example cuz Claude's got a little
bit of a better eye for design. You're
going to end up with a website looks
like this gorgeous gradient very
professional very smart. We scroll down
and we should have this beautiful
animation. Look at that guys. That is
really crisp. Then as you come down, you
got these different logos, three stages,
strategy, positioning, brand new XUI.
Again, leveraging all the skills that
we've given it using this Higful feature
to generate the videos. Absolutely
gorgeous. Really freaking crisp. Looks
fantastic. And if I do, you know what? I
really like Look at this. My favorite
bits of this as well. I love that we can
just like add these things in really
premium, really freaking crisp. We can
do anything we want to. Then we can come
back over literally to the chat window
and publish this on a website very
simply by coming over here. We could
say, "Hey, sounds awesome. Create a
brand new GitHub repo using the GitHub
CLI and then use my Versel CLI to go
ahead and publish this and create a
website. And if you're not sure what all
this stuff means, I'll put a link on
screen for my codeex full master class
that get you 99% of skills. If you
didn't click on it earlier, it'll be
down below in the description. Um, so
you can literally learn how to do all
this stuff very quickly. And so what
we've basically done here, we've wired
up, we've connected the skills. Every
tool that we've used in this stack has
basically become a callable skill that
we can enshrine by basically explaining
you've done an excellent job. Now turn
this into a reusable skill. All right,
we can animate any image. We can clone
and narate things with voice. We could
use so many different features. It's
really freaking cool. And what we do
fundamentally is turn it into a skill.
Run the workflow once, save as a
skill.md, and then it will auto run the
next time. So the core idea here for
your content operating system is that we
build it once, we get it to a great
standard and then we can reuse it
forever. That could be client websites
like I just showed you. Animated ads,
sell pages, course content, UGC content,
product launches, pitch decks, brand
systems, you name it, we can literally
build it now. So what is all this sort
of cost? So I had a look at the Hixel
pricing. Obviously there's a cost using
Hixold if you're going down that route.
Any kind of video gen, there's going to
be something on there. So if you're
doing annual is $15 a month for 200
credits. Um $39 gives you,200 credits.
So it's kind of like I guess almost four
times the price for six times the
credits. Um and then you can pretty much
decide if you want starter plus or ultra
just to give you an idea and a sense of
what that actually costs. Okay. So
firstly let's say that you wanted to do
something with Nana Banana 2. Okay. And
you wanted to do 2K which is a minimum
and you wanted to do four iterations
that is 8 credits. Likewise if you're
doing a video with Cans for I don't know
let's say 5 seconds for instance that
would be 45 credits just to give you a
sense of what the actual price is. And
once again, I'll put it down here. N9
Pro image is two credits. Cling 3.06.
And you get a kind of great idea of how
that all connects together. So now
you've learned exactly how to build
these beautiful videos with Claude Code
and Hicksfield and build this really
cool freaking AI content system. The
next thing that we're going to want to
do then is build on these skills by
making our websites incredible, which
you can do by watching this video right